<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions Nato 1
-->
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_ace21_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Galil ACE family is designed and produced by the Israeli arms company IWI Ltd. The basis of the ACE Galil rifles is the Galil assault rifle, which in its turn is based on Kalashnikov's AK rifle. The Galil ACE focuses on ergonomics, ease of use and integration with additional attachments, as well as flexibility in combat - the Galil ACE family includes the three most common types of ammunition in the world (5.56x45 NATO, 7.62x39 M43 and NATO 7.62x51), with multiple barrel lengths for each type. This particular variant utilises 5.56x45 NATO rounds and has a compact barrel. In the Zone, this assault rifle is a real rarity.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak102_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-102 is a 5.56x45mm carbine version of the AK-101 rifle. It features a shortened barrel that makes it a middle ground between a full rifle and the more compact AKS-74U. The rifle's receiver is made of stamped steel; magazine is made out of reinforced fibreglass and the stock is made of hollow plastic; making it lighter, more durable, and allowing a field kit to be stored inside of  it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip", Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553, EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The 92F is perhaps best known as the standard pistol of the US Military, replacing the legendary M1911. It is a short-recoil operated, locked-breech weapon with an aluminium frame and a hard chromed barrel bore. A popular sidearm adopted by several countries, it is especially popular among criminals for its high-powered rounds and high-capacity magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_stars_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The 92F is perhaps best known as the standard pistol of the US Military, replacing the legendary M1911. It is a short-recoil operated, locked-breech weapon with an aluminium frame and a hard chromed barrel bore. A popular sidearm adopted by several countries, it is especially popular among criminals for its high-powered rounds and high-capacity magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DOCTER Sight III, Deltapoint PRO , Trijicon RMR.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_m9_descr">	<!-- wpn_beretta_modern in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. This is the US Marine Corps version of the Italian Beretta 92FS, made by demands from said faction. Since it is famous around Mercenaries, Freedom and some strange mentioned recent faction, it's safe to say that the way this "semi-prototype" got in The Zone is through Western armies' deserters and ex-PMCs.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The 92F is perhaps best known as the standard pistol of the US Military, replacing the legendary M1911. It is a short-recoil operated, locked-breech weapon with an aluminium frame and a hard chromed barrel bore. A popular sidearm adopted by several countries, it is especially popular among criminals for its high-powered rounds and high-capacity magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_browning_mk3_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Browning Hi-Power Mark III is a modernization of the classic Browning HP, made in 1988. It is also the standard issue gun of the Australian Defence Force. The big change here would be better reliability, which the original Browning sadly awfully needed so, and better ironsights, improved action as well as improved recoil. In terms of The Zone, it is a classic gun, a jack-of-all-trades, almost every faction tended to use it back before the First Siege of Chernobyl, but strangely during the Second Siege of Chernobyl, it was incredibly rare until finally a new big supplement of it came after the travel to the Road to the North.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_browning_p35_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Browning Hi-Power is a single-action, 9mm semi-automatic pistol. It is based on the ideas of American firearms inventor John Browning, created and patented in 1922, later patented by FN Herstal. Browning died in 1926, before he had finished developing a production version, but FN arms designer Dieudonne Saive fully developed it. The Hi-Power pistol was noted for its 13 round magazine capacity, twice that of contemporary designs such as the Luger or Mauser 1910. From the blueing finish and the "barrel sights", it is clear this is a classic, original P-35 made in Belgium.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M1911 was the standard-issue side arm for the US military from 1911 to 1985. An extremely reliable and robust weapon, it's been adopted for military, police and civilian use around the world and remains a very popular firearm to this day.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911a1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An improvement of the 1911, after criticism from World War I and outside of it too, reissued to the U.S. Military in 1924. One major issue that the 1911 had was the hammer, since the guard was made too small, there was a high chance of getting a "hammer bite". For that, a longer "beaver tail" has been made. Also, the safety grip has been changed to be more ergonomic, it has a cutout near the frame to help with different hand shapes, a smaller trigger for less force application, wider ironsights and simplified checkered grips. All these changes, some are controversial like the new safety grip and the trigger, but the hammer guard and ironsights are a big improvement. You simply can't go wrong with this pistol, though some still prefer the original 1911 and find their own ways to avoid the flaws on those, such as gripping it one-handed to avoid hammer bites.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M1911 was the standard-issue side arm for the US military from 1911 to 1985. An extremely reliable and robust weapon, it's been adopted for military, police and civilian use around the world and remains a very popular firearm to this day. This is a unique model with red stains on dark-beige colour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This is the original Colt 1911, made by John Moses Browning in 1910 and patented the next year, hence the 1911 designation. Coming to service in 1913, this is considered to be the very first self-loading handgun that is vastly successful, being able to use the .45 ACP and shoot at least 1000 rounds flawlessly. You can tell it's a classic 1911 and not an 1911A1 by the fact it has a smaller ejection port, longer trigger and especially the diamond-shaped grip, also its only magazine of 7, keep it with you. Thanks to the black market going on in The Zone, this true classic has been acquired, though it might have been modified a bit, good luck figuring that out. If you want accuracy using a strong caliber without too much recoil, this might be for you, but it's best used as a backup gun if anything, since it has no way to have a suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_duty_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M1911 was the standard-issue side arm for the US military from 1911 to 1985. An extremely reliable and robust weapon, it's been adopted for military, police and civilian use around the world and remains a very popular firearm to this day. This variant has a distinctive feature - it's more powerful than the normal one.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_merc_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M1911 was the standard-issue side arm for the US military from 1911 to 1985. An extremely reliable and robust weapon, it's been adopted for military, police and civilian use around the world and remains a very popular firearm to this day. This model is considerably more reliable and accurate.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in .45 ACP. An improved version of a classic semi-automatic pistol. The weapon's only drawback is it's mediocre magazine capacity which is largely compensated by the hard-hitting ammo it uses.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_tokarev_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A "Russian version" of the 1911. The only difference here would be that it has different markings, but this seems to be an old variant where it has no Cyrillic stamp indicating it's the version ordered from USA to Russia. It is identical to the 1911, but one key and important difference is the fact the magazine and barrel is slightly modified, which in turn can be further modified easily by any technician to change the caliber from .45 ACP to 7.62x25mm Tokarev.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]FN FAL is a NATO firearm produced in Belgium by Fabrique Nationale de Herstal. One of the most recognized and popular automatic rifles. The FN FAL was originally developed for an intermediate 7.92x33 mm cartridge used by the Germans during World War II, then prototypes for the .280 British cartridge appeared. It was later remade chambered for 7.62x51 mm NATO, adopted as a single patron for NATO countries. During the Cold War, it received the nickname "the right hand of the free world."\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fnc_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FNC (Fabrique Nationale Carabine) is a 5.56x45mm NATO assault rifle developed by the Belgian arms manufacturer FN Herstal and introduced in the late 1970s.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Formally accepted into service with the IDF in 1972, the IMI Galil is designed for operation in arid conditions and is based on the Finnish RK 62, which itself was derived from the Soviet AK-47. The Galil is noted for its reliability in combat conditions, and ease of maintenance. It has a line chambered for 5.56x45mm and one for 7.62x51mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Galil 4x scope (after modification).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Formally accepted into service with the IDF in 1972, the IMI Galil is designed for operation in arid conditions and is based on the Finnish RK 62, which itself was derived from the Soviet AK-47. The Galil is noted for its reliability in combat conditions, and ease of maintenance. It has a line chambered for 5.56x45mm and one for 7.62x51mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Galil 4x scope.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Formally accepted into service with the IDF in 1972, the IMI Galil is designed for operation in arid conditions and is based on the Finnish RK 62, which itself was derived from the Soviet AK-47. The Galil is noted for its reliability in combat conditions, and ease of maintenance. It has a line chambered for 5.56x45mm and one for 7.62x51mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Galil 4x scope.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g3_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The G3A3 is a battle rifle developed in the 1950s by the German arms manufacturer Heckler & Koch GmbH in collaboration with the Spanish state owned design and development agency CETME (Centro de Estudios Tecnicos de Materiales Especiales). It is designed to use the 7.62x51mm NATO round, and uses a Roller-delayed blowback action. The rifle owes its design to the CETME mod. A, which was designed by the german engineer Dr. Ludwig Vorgrimler. In 1957, Heckler & Koch bought the license to manufacture the rifle, where small modifications were made to the CETME design. Officially adopted into service in 1959, by the Bundeswehr as the G3, it remained in service until 1995 when it was replaced by the G36. Despite having been officially replaced by the German army, it is still in limited use.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g43_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Adopting a simple gas-operated mechanism from Soviet SVT rifles, Nazi Germany developed the Gewehr 43 semi-automatic rifle. It was renamed Karabiner 43 in 1944. Equipped with the ZF 4 telescopic sight, it is an effective sniper rifle.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ZF-41 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_hk417_descr"> <!-- NOT IN GAMMA ? -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Heckler & Koch HK417 is a battle rifle designed and manufactured by Heckler & Koch in Germany. It is the larger caliber version of the HK416, and chambered for the full-power 7.62x51mm NATO rifle cartridge. It is a gas-operated, selective fire rifle with a rotating bolt. The HK417 is intended for use in roles where the greater penetrative power, stopping power, and range of the 7.62x51mm cartridge are required. It has been adopted for service by a number of armed forces, special forces, and police organizations.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Browning Hi-Power is a single-action, 9mm semi-automatic pistol. It is based on the ideas of American firearms inventor John Browning, created and patented in 1922, later patented by FN Herstal. Browning died in 1926, before he had finished developing a production version, but FN arms designer Dieudonne Saive fully developed it. The Hi-Power pistol was noted for its 13 round magazine capacity, twice that of contemporary designs such as the Luger or Mauser 1910. This modified variant of the Browning HP pistol, despite its venerable age, enjoys popularity around the world.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ithacam37_stakeout_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Ithaca M37 is one of most recognized pump-action shotguns of the United States and has the longest production run for a pump-action shotgun in history. Designed for civilians, police and military alike, the Ithaca 37 is based on a 1915 patent by firearms designer John Browning, initially named the Remington Model 17. This shotgun utilizes a novel combination ejection and loading port on the bottom of the gun, leaving the sides closed to the elements. The "Stakeout" varient features an officially shortened 330mm barrel and uses a pistol grip stock.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_1]Ithaca Gun Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1937\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ithacam37_sawnoff_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Ithaca M37 is one of most recognized pump-action shotguns of the United States and has the longest production run for a pump-action shotgun in history. Designed for civilians, police and military alike, the Ithaca 37 is based on a 1915 patent by firearms designer John Browning, initially named the Remington Model 17. This shotgun utilizes a novel combination ejection and loading port on the bottom of the gun, leaving the sides closed to the elements. This model has had the stock unofficially sawn-off to reduce weight.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_1]Ithaca Gun Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1937\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ithacam37_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Ithaca M37 is one of most recognized pump-action shotguns of the United States and has the longest production run for a pump-action shotgun in history. Designed for civilians, police and military alike, the Ithaca 37 is based on a 1915 patent by firearms designer John Browning, initially named the Remington Model 17. This shotgun utilizes a novel combination ejection and loading port on the bottom of the gun, leaving the sides closed to the elements. The "Riot" model is widely considered the standard issue M37.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_1]Ithaca Gun Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1937\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ithacam37_extmag_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Ithaca M37 is one of most recognized pump-action shotguns of the United States and has the longest production run for a pump-action shotgun in history. Designed for civilians, police and military alike, the Ithaca 37 is based on a 1915 patent by firearms designer John Browning, initially named the Remington Model 17. This shotgun utilizes a novel combination ejection and loading port on the bottom of the gun, leaving the sides closed to the elements. The "Defense" variant adds a 7-round extended magazine and uses polymer instead of wood, with a stainless steel finish.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_1]Ithaca Gun Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1937\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]ATTACHMENTS (INTEGRATED):\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[0,255,255,255]Extended Magazine\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ithacam37_trench_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Ithaca M37 is one of most recognized pump-action shotguns of the United States and has the longest production run for a pump-action shotgun in history. Designed for civilians, police and military alike, the Ithaca 37 is based on a 1915 patent by firearms designer John Browning, initially named the Remington Model 17. This shotgun utilizes a novel combination ejection and loading port on the bottom of the gun, leaving the sides closed to the elements. The "Trenchgun" variant sports a heatshield and bayonet lug, helping the gun stay cool and providing better grip.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_1]Ithaca Gun Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1937\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]During World War II, certain Karabiner 98k rifles were selected for their exceptional accuracy and fitted with the ZF39 telescopic sight. These rifles were used by Nazi Germany as sniper rifles. In skilled hands, they had an effective range of up to 1000 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ZF-4 Scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A1 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A1 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 NATO compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_alt_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A1 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A1 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A1 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A1 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. The L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenariosand is recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using the standard issue SUSAT telescopic sight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT for native L85 mount only.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A1 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A1 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT 4x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 NATO compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_alt_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT 4x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT 4x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 NATO compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The improved L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SUSAT 4x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Based on the AR-15, the LR-300 is an excellent weapon system suitable for military use in close quarters battle. Its folding skeletal stock makes it ideal for aggressive and rapid building entries requiring a compact yet powerful selective fire weapon. With excellent ergonomics and lightweight, this weapon is highly accurate but it is sensitive to dirt and is not ideal for difficult field conditions.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Based on the AR-15, the LR-300 is an excellent weapon system suitable for military use in close quarters battle. Its folding skeletal stock makes it ideal for aggressive and rapid building entries requiring a compact yet powerful selective fire weapon. With excellent ergonomics and lightweight, this weapon is highly accurate but it is sensitive to dirt and is not ideal for difficult field conditions.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Based on the AR-15, the LR-300 is an excellent weapon system suitable for military use in close quarters battle. Its folding skeletal stock makes it ideal for aggressive and rapid building entries requiring a compact yet powerful selective fire weapon. With excellent ergonomics and lightweight, this weapon is highly accurate but it is sensitive to dirt and is not ideal for difficult field conditions.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to earlier carbine versions of the M16, all based on the original AR-15 made by ArmaLite. It is a shorter and lighter version of the M16 assault rifle, sharing 80% of its parts. The M4 fires 5.56x45mm NATO ammunition and are gas operated, air cooled, magazine fed, selective fire firearms with a 4 position telescoping stock. As with many carbines, the M4 is handy and more convenient to carry than a full length rifle. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_freedom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_siber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The M4 carbine is a gas operated, air cooled, magazine fed, selective fire carbine with a 4 position telescoping stock. Due to it's shorter length, it is more convenient to carry than a full length rifle.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m16_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M16 is the U.S. military designation for a family of rifles derived from the ArmaLite AR-15 and further developed by Colt starting in the 1960s. The M16 rifle family including the M16/A1/A2/A3/A4 has been the primary infantry rifle of the United States military since the 1960s. With its variants, it has been in use by 15 NATO countries, and is the most produced firearm in its calibre. The M16 is a lightweight, 5.56x45mm calibre, air cooled, gas operated, magazine fed assault rifle, with a rotating bolt, actuated by direct impingement gas operation. The rifle is made of steel, aluminium, and composite plastics.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M16A2 rifle entered service in the 1980s, chambered to fire the standard NATO round, the Belgian designed M855/M856 cartridge. The M16A2 is a select fire rifle, incorporating design elements requested by the Marine Corps: an adjustable, windage rear sight, longer stock, heavier barrel, case deflector for left-hand shooters and cylindrical hand guards. The M16A2 is manufactured by Colt and the Fabrique Nationale de Herstal arms company, with the variant rifles made elsewhere in the world.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m79_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M79 grenade launcher is a single shot, shoulder-fired, break-action grenade launcher that fires a 40x46mm grenade, which uses what the US Army calls the High-Low Propulsion System to keep recoil low. First appeared during the Vietnam War.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP5 is one of the most famous and wide spread firearms of its class. The MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favourite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organisations the world over. The MP5A3 is fitted with a retractable metal stock. Not surprisingly, having flooded the global black markets, it eventually made its way to the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EoTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP5 is one of the most famous and wide spread firearms of its class. The MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favourite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organisations the world over. The MP5A3 is fitted with a retractable metal stock. Not surprisingly, having flooded the global black markets, it eventually made its way to the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EoTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the MP5 with an integrated suppressor. In the Zone, mercenaries prefer this variant to the normal one.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] MP5SD suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Mossberg 590 was developed by O.F.Mossberg & sons company during 1970s in US as a modification of the Mossberg model 500 shotgun for adoption by the US Military. Modifications included strengthening of the receiver, installation of the vented heatshield around the barrel, a bayonet lug and extended magazine and an aluminium trigger guard instead of plastic one. Standard finish is Parkerizing, and the gun is provided with replacement pistol grip, which allows easy conversion to 'Cruiser' modification. Since 1987, this was the standard shotgun of US Armed forces; officially replaced in US Army with Benelli M1014 semi-automatic shotgun, Mossberg 590 shotguns are still used by US Navy and US Marine Corp.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta is a rotating cylinder fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and combat. The weapon benefits from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, but its bulkiness and considerable weight, combined with a long reload time, are the price to be paid for these advantages. Used in the Zone and used primarily to clear confined spaces of mutants.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta is a rotating cylinder fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and combat. The weapon benefits from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, but its bulkiness and considerable weight, combined with a long reload time, are the price to be paid for these advantages. Used in the Zone and used primarily to clear confined spaces of mutants.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta is a rotating cylinder fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and combat. The weapon benefits from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, but its bulkiness and considerable weight, combined with a long reload time, are the price to be paid for these advantages. Used in the Zone and used primarily to clear confined spaces of mutants.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]There are many options for a different rifle cartridge. Standard cartridge - 7.62x51 mm NATO (.308 Win). Technically, it is a magazine rifle with a longitudinally sliding rotary bolt. Store capacity depends on the caliber and can be from 3 to 5. It is a top product from Remington Arms.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defense Wave QD compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Remington 870 is an American gun first introduced in 1950 by Remington Arms. Due to its characteristic recharge is one of the most famous pump-action rifles in the world. Produced in various versions, it is suitable for both the military and the police, for hunters and athletes, as well as for self-defense.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SG 552 Commando is designed for urban combat, making it the most compact member of SIG's renowned SG 550 family, which enhances its CQC capabilities.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552t_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SG 552 Commando is designed for urban combat, making it the most compact member of SIG's renowned SG 550 family, which enhances its CQC capabilities.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SPAS-12 is a dual-mode shotgun, designed for combat and anti-riot measures. It is employed by many special military and police units around the world. With its distinctive heat shield and folding stock, the SPAS-12 is an iconic firearm. Notable for its reliability and tactical flexibility. Despite its heavy weight, complex mechanism and considerable cost, it is in demand in the Zone due to its effectiveness against mutants.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_descr_new">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SPAS-12 is a dual-mode shotgun, designed for combat and anti-riot measures. It is employed by many special military and police units around the world. With its distinctive heat shield and folding stock, the SPAS-12 is an iconic firearm. Notable for its reliability and tactical flexibility. Despite its heavy weight, complex mechanism and considerable cost, it is in demand in the Zone due to its effectiveness against mutants.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Salvo 12 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_1921_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Thompson is a blowback-operated, air-cooled, magazine-fed selective-fire submachine gun.\n
		This variant of the Thompson also nicknamed as the "Chicago Typewriter" features a faster firerate and the Blish Lock system for weapon operation.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_m1a1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Thompson is a blowback-operated, air-cooled, magazine-fed selective-fire submachine gun.\n
		This variant of the Thompson has a significantly reduced firerate and a simplified design produced on request of the US Army. As a result, the Blish lock, oiling system and compensator were removed. Despite having a slower firerate, the gun is much worse to shoot than the 1921.\n
		This variant also has a different receiver than the 1921/1928 variant and thus will not accept drum mags.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The UMP was developed in the 1990s, first appearing on the market in 1999. Providing greater stopping power than the MP5, the UMP45 also produces more recoil. This makes controlling full automatic fire more difficult. The UMP45's cyclic rate of fire was lowered significantly to combat this problem.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The UMP was developed in the 1990s, first appearing on the market in 1999. Providing greater stopping power than the MP5, the UMP45 also produces more recoil. This makes controlling full automatic fire more difficult. The UMP45's cyclic rate of fire was lowered significantly to combat this problem.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium rear sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_winchester1873_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Winchester 1873 lever-action rifle, often referred to as the "Gun that Won the West," is a historic and iconic firearm introduced in 1873 by the Winchester Repeating Arms Company. Known for its reliability and innovation, this rifle played a significant role in the American frontier and beyond. Chambered in various popular calibers of the time, such as .44-40 and .38-40, it featured a distinctive lever mechanism that allowed for rapid and efficient reloading, making it a favorite among cowboys, lawmen, and outlaws alike. Its elegant design, smooth action, and remarkable durability contributed to its legendary status, making it a prized collector's item today. The Winchester 1873 lever-action rifle symbolizes the spirit of the Wild West and remains an enduring symbol of American firearm history. Adapted to use both .357 ammunition and a modern scope for easier access.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: PSO-1 Scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_xm4_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to earlier carbine versions of the M16, all based on the original AR-15 made by ArmaLite. It is a shorter and lighter version of the M16 assault rifle, sharing 80% of its parts. The M4 fires 5.56x45mm NATO ammunition and are gas operated, air cooled, magazine fed, selective fire firearms with a 4 position telescoping stock. As with many carbines, the M4 is handy and more convenient to carry than a full length rifle. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PN-23, SpecterDR, OKP-07 (picatinny), ACOG x4, EOTech XPS3-0, Meprolight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.\n</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions Nato 2
-->

	<string id="st_wpn_ace52_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51, the ACE 52 has been built to meet the needs of the modern battlefield making it a convinient choice for armies and agents seeking advanced rifles. Heralded as the ultimate assault weapon, this rifle has been battle-proven under the most adverse and extreme conditions. Although based upon the IMI Galils of old, advanced design and performance mechanisms transformed the ACE 52 into a more reliable and highly accurate weapon for combat warfare. These new ACE variants feature better ergonomics and accuracy due to their integration of steel with polymer instead of using a machined solid steel billet action.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The AK-101 is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the logistical compatibility and familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov. It is designed with modern and composite materials, including plastics to reduce weight and to improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The AK-101 is marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the logistical compatibility and familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov. It is designed with modern and composite materials, including plastics to reduce weight and to improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_9mm_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. Also known as the Steyr AUG Para. It comes with a different unique barrel, bolt and magazine, although a TMP magazine can fit with it. This weapon was made for, as the name would tell, Paratroopers. It is a reliable sub-machinegun, in bullpup format, which is why it's popular amongst Freedomers.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium rear sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. Steyr AUG A1 in standard Austrian Army rifle configuration (tan colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch).\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] STEYR UMS compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. Steyr AUG A1 in CQB configuration. It has less weight and an increased rate of fire compared to the base A1 model.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] STEYR UMS compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. The AUG A2 is an improvement of the A1. One of the key differences is the replacement of the integral scope with a Picatinny rail, allowing all sorts of iron and reflex sights, as well as scopes, to be added. It is a common rifle to find in the black market, and a very reliable one.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. Steyr AUG A3 is a further improvement of both the A1 and A2. Having the same Picatinny Rail integration as the A2 in full-length, as well as coming with an external bolt release located above the magwell, the rifle is easily able to fit any ironsight or reflex sight, including any scope.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. Steyr AUG A3 in standard rifle configuration. It differs from the A1 model with the presence of four Picatinny rails.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] STEYR UMS compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
<!--	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units. This model has been modified for usage of 7.62x51 NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
-->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_thales_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. The Thales F90, also known as the EF88, is an improvement of the Australian version of the AUG, the F88 Austeyr. Produced in 2012 and meant to replace the F88, this is the most modern AUG one can find, having a lot of improvements based on the performance of the F88 itself, which increases its ergonomics and reliability. The unique barrel gives it much better recoil control and accuracy, while the custom foregrip allows for better handling. An incredibly rare gun, brought in by some ex-Australian Spec Ops, for that the price is right.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_px4_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. The Px4 Storm is an advancement of the Beretta 8000, meant to be as a replacer of the 92FS for personal defense and law enforcement use. Its rotating barrel allows for better recoil control and continuous shots, the lightframe also helps with the weight. This particular model seems to come with tritium sights as well. From the looks of it, these weapons were "illegally" exported from Armenia and Romania, by mercenaries that used to be part of the police force from said countries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt_kimber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An advanced variant of the Colt M1911A1 developed by Kimber Manufacturing. The Desert Warrior was made for conducting special operations by the USA.</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51mm. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms). This model comes with 21" barrel. This model is used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
	    %c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_aus_tri_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51mm. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms). This model comes with 21" barrel. This model is used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
	    %c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded using a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG x4 & Canted Aimpoint T1.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_fal_leup_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51mm. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms). This model comes with 21" barrel. This model is used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
	    %c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded using a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope & Canted Aimpoint T1.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_sa5x_spec_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51mm. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms). This model comes with 21" barrel. This model is used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
	    %c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded using a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Elcan SpecterDr Scope & Canted Aimpoint T1.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_famas3_descr">
        <text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]FAMAS stands for Fusil d'Assaut de la Manufacture d'Armes de St-Etienne (Assault Rifle by St-Etienne Arms Factory). Development of this rifle began in 1967, by Paul Tellie, a French arms designer. This new rifle was intended to replace the ageing MAS Mle.49/56 semi-automatic rifles, MAT-49 submachine guns and MAC Mle.1929 light machine guns. The first FAMAS prototype had been built in 1971, and French military began to test this rifle in 1972. Meanwhile, France adopted a Swiss-designed SIG SG-540 5.56mm assault rifle as an intermediate solution. The FAMAS was adopted by the French in 1978 and since then became a standard French Army rifle, known among the French soldiers as "Le Clairon" (the bulge).\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN2000 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000e_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN2000 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000e_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN2000 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000e_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN2000 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36">
		<text>G36</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_descr"> <!-- OLD G36 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hensoldt ZF Dual Optic (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36v_rwap">
		<text>G36 RMR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36v_rwap_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hensoldt ZF Scope & RMR (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k">
		<text>G36C</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k_descr"> <!-- OLD G36c -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance. The C-varient comes with a much shorter barrel than the original, providing better handling and lower weight while trading for worse recoil and accuracy. Best used for close encounters, though still not a bad weapon for long-range combat. The G36C was made to be a further improvement of G36K. It is a true favourite among SWAT operatives and has shown to be very useful in Urban Combat. It comes with a peculiar ironsight, indicating that this is the Lithuanian version and was most likely smuggled into the zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36c_rwap">
		<text>G36C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36c_rwap_descr"> 
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance. The C-varient comes with a much shorter barrel than the original, providing better handling and lower weight while trading for worse recoil and accuracy. Best used for close encounters, though still not a bad weapon for long-range combat. The G36C was made to be a further improvement of G36K. It is a true favourite among SWAT operatives and has shown to be very useful in Urban Combat. It comes with a peculiar ironsight, indicating that this is the Lithuanian version and was most likely smuggled into the zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_camo">
		<text>G36K</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_camo_descr"> <!-- OLD G36K -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Carbine (K stands for "kurz", short) version of the G36. Having a shorter barrel than the original, it gives better handling and lower weight while having a slightly worse recoil and accuracy, but still not detrimental. It also has no integrated scope, instead, it comes with ironsights packed with picatinny rails fit for many NATO scopes. This variant is the most popular amongst every user, be it Military or Law Enforcement, considered a massive improvement over the G36.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36ka4_rwap">
		<text>G36K</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36ka4_rwap_descr"> <!-- NEW G36K -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance. The K-varient comes with a shorter barrel, fitted with an open type flash suppressor, a shorter forend and a bottom rail that can be used to attach tactical accessories such as a UTL flashlight. The rifle's barrel lacks the ability to launch rifle grenades and will not support a bayonet.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.
		</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k_rwap">
		<text>G36K</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36k_rwap_descr"> <!-- NEW G36K WITH GRIP -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in the early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance. The K-varient comes with a shorter barrel, fitted with an open type flash suppressor, a shorter forend and a bottom rail that can be used to attach tactical accessories such as a UTL flashlight. The rifle's barrel lacks the ability to launch rifle grenades and will not support a bayonet.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_descr"> <!-- OLD G36 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]BLACKMARKET OLD VERSION</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_c_descr"> <!-- OLD G36C -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]BLACKMARKET OLD VERSION</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_k_descr"> <!-- OLD G36K -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]BLACKMARKET OLD VERSION</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A sniper variant of the G3. The "SG" stands for Scharfschutzengewehr, or "sharpshooting rifle". The rifles were individually selected from the production line for their accuracy and then modified. A Zeiss 1.5-6x variable power telescopic sight was added using a HK claw mount attached to the receiver. The stock was extended slightly and comes with a heavy, dual-stage buffer and adjustable cheek rest. A special set trigger group was added for a crisp trigger pull of 1 lb. Automatic fire was retained.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] G3 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Glock 19 is a smaller version of the Glock 17. Its reduced size made the Glock 19 easier to conceal and carry by military and police forces. The pistol was debuted by Glock GbmH of Austria in 1988. When compared to the Glock 17, the Glock 19 retains the weight of its slide to keep the short recoil operation in check while at the same time shortening the grip and barrel. Many components of the Glock 19 were made interchangeable with the Glock 17, including the magazine. Simply put, the Glock 19 is a compact version of the 17.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Glock 19 is a smaller version of the Glock 17. Its reduced size made the Glock 19 easier to conceal and carry by military and police forces. The pistol was debuted by Glock GbmH of Austria in 1988. When compared to the Glock 17, the Glock 19 retains the weight of its slide to keep the short recoil operation in check while at the same time shortening the grip and barrel. Many components of the Glock 19 were made interchangeable with the Glock 17, including the magazine. Simply put, the Glock 19 is a compact version of the 17.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Glock 19 is a smaller version of the Glock 17. Its reduced size made the Glock 19 easier to conceal and carry by military and police forces. The pistol was debuted by Glock GbmH of Austria in 1988. When compared to the Glock 17, the Glock 19 retains the weight of its slide to keep the short recoil operation in check while at the same time shortening the grip and barrel. Many components of the Glock 19 were made interchangeable with the Glock 17, including the magazine. Simply put, the Glock 19 is a compact version of the 17. This model has an optional automatic fire mode.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A classic of a polymer-framed, short recoil-operated pistol, the Glock 17, Gen 4 variant if the slide engraving wasn't obvious, designed and produced by Austrian manufacturer Glock Ges.m.b.H. This firearm entered Austrian military and police service by 1982 after it was the top performer in reliability and safety tests. Ever since then, it has been exported to many other countries, including Ukraine itself for the Special Forces. Due to its low weight, very good recoil and 9mm caliber, this is a very popular pistol among every faction and rightly so.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The HK416 is a rifle designed and manufactured by Heckler & Koch to improve the M4. It is available as a complete firearm, or as an upper receiver that fits on any AR-15 type lower receiver. The US Army's Delta Force collaborated with the German arms makers to develop the new rifle. Testing the H&K 416 in 2004 revealed that the piston operating system significantly reduces malfunctions while increasing the life of parts. The project was originally called the H&K M4, but was changed in response to a trademark infringement suit filed by Colt Defence. Currently, it is only available to government and military organisations, hence why this assault rifle is usually carried by Mercenaries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_hs2000_short">
		<text>HS-2000</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_hs2000_descr"> <!-- wpn_glock_modern in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The HS2000 is a Croatian-made pistol, manufactured by HS Produkt. It has a polymer frame and fires based on a Striker, which is similar to the Glock pistols. Although despite being a HS2000, this is actually a HS-9 4.0 G2, which is a civilian version of the HS2000 itself out for the market. This is due to Black Market manufacturing, the internals are clearly HS2000 while the rest is simply marked as HS-9, it also comes with an ambidextrous setup. This pistol was being manufactured in 1995, until it got released in 1999. After 2001, the Police and Army of Croatia deecided to adopt it, becoming their national gun. In USA, it is known as the "Springfield XD".  \n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more organomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by March tactical.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical Scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_silen98_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more organomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by March tactical and has the mount for a suppressor installed.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical Scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] K98 Forester compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. The L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenariosand is recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using the standard issue SUSAT telescopic sight. This version has been installed with picatinny rails for use with modern sights and optics.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m249_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M249 is a belt fed 5.56x45 machine gun. It is the American adaptation of the Belgian FN Minimi. The M249 has seen action in every major conflict involving the United States since the U.S. invasion of Panama in 1989. Soldiers are generally satisfied with the weapon's performance, though there have been reports of clogging with dirt and sand.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mk14_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]United States Navy Mark 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle (Mk 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle, "improved combat rifle") - American Marksman rifle, created by special operations of the US Navy based on the M14 rifle. Used by a number of special units of the Navy, including SEAL.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp7_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Heckler & Koch MP7 (Maschinenpistole 7) is a German personal defence weapon (PDW) designed and manufactured by Heckler & Koch (H&K) and chambered for the HK 4.6x30mm cartridge. It was designed with the new cartridge to meet NATO requirements published in 1989, as these requirements call for a personal defense weapon (PDW) class firearm, with a greater ability to penetrate body armor than current weapons limited to conventional pistol cartridges. The MP7 went into production in 2001.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical aiming laser module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp7_descr_new">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Heckler & Koch MP7 (Maschinenpistole 7) is a German personal defence weapon (PDW) designed and manufactured by Heckler & Koch (H&K) and chambered for the HK 4.6x30mm cartridge. It was designed with the new cartridge to meet NATO requirements published in 1989, as these requirements call for a personal defense weapon (PDW) class firearm, with a greater ability to penetrate body armor than current weapons limited to conventional pistol cartridges. The MP7 went into production in 2001.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m45_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modern variant of the M1911, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. This idea of a better 1911 came in the late 1980s, from the USMC Colonel, Robert Young. It is pretty much an M1911A1 assembled by many manufacturers, since it has the slide from Springfield Armory, Mag Extract & Release from Wilson Combat and everything else from Nowlin Manufacturing. The results, while sounding like "Frankenstein Monster" of a description, actually does make a pretty pistol that is better than the 1911. The Mercenaries favour it much so for the fact it's heavily customizable, the betterments are just bonuses.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m45a1_descr"> <!-- wpn_colt1911_merc in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modern variant of the M1911 and an improvement of the M45, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. Compared to the M45, the improvements the M45A1 has is the dual recoil spring system that spreads out the recoil force of the .45 ACP round by lowering the peak force of the recoil pulse, the 3-dot red tritium night sights, a 5-inch national match barrel, ambidextrous safety, picatinny rail for the frame and a desert tan Cerakote finish. You wonder how the desert tan Ceratoke finish even fits in The Zone, but it might be a Mercenary's pride.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_gs">
		<text>FN P90</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_gs_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities did not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low. FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was the FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with the improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Ring Sights MC-10-80 (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_aim_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta is a rotating cylinder fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and combat. The weapon benefits from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, but its bulkiness and considerable weight, combined with a long reload time, are the price to be paid for these advantages. Used in the Zone and used primarily to clear confined spaces of mutants. Sacrificing rate of fire, stopping power is increased. This model comes with an Aimpoint AB collimator sight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 sight (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_archangel_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has the Promag Archangel polymer stock installed.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Promag Archangel polymer stock kit installed.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defense Wave QD compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_magpul_pro_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has the Magpul PRO 700 chassis and additional Trijicon RMR Red Dot Sight installed on it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magpul "PRO 700" chassis kit installed.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defense Wave QD compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_mod_x_gen3_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has the MOD X GEN III Modular Rifle System and additional Leupold DeltaPoint PRO Red Dot Sight installed on it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] MOD X Gen.3 chassis kit installed.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defense Wave QD compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG-Sauer P220, manufactured in the late 1970s by J.P. Sauer & Son Company, is often considered the best out of the box .45 calibre double action pistol. An instant success, the P220 was adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and by many European police organisations. This pistol also found its way into the US, first through the Browning Arms Company of Utah and since the 1980s, through the SIGARMS Company of New Hampshire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_custom_descr"> <!-- Actually st_wpn_sig229 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG-Sauer P220, manufactured in the late 1970s by J.P. Sauer & Son Company, is often considered the best out of the box .45 calibre double action pistol. An instant success, the P220 was adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and by many European police organisations. This pistol also found its way into the US, first through the Browning Arms Company of Utah and since the 1980s, through the SIGARMS Company of New Hampshire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium front sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG-Sauer P220 is often considered the best out of the box .45 caliber double action pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_upg220_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG-Sauer P220 is often considered the best out of the box .45 caliber double action pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded using a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC Black Box compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_u2p2g0r_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG-Sauer P220 is often considered the best out of the box .45 caliber double action pistol.This pistol has been fitted with a Threaded barrel for use with a Black Box suppressor, Tritium sights and Viridian X5L laser sight and high capacity 19 round magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded using a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC Black Box compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SIG Sauer P226R is a full-sized, service-type pistol chambered for the 9x19mm Parabellum, features a Picatinny rail mount on the underside of the frame.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_226sig_kit_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. The SIG Sauer P226R is a full-sized, service-type pistol made by SIG Sauer, a standard service weapon of Navy SEALs. Features a Picatinny rail mount on the underside of a frame.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Trijicon RMR Red Dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Osprey-9 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig229_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The P229 is a compact-sized, 9mm caliber chambered, upgraded P228, meant for police duty and conceal carry. Since this is the "LEGION" variant, it's safe to assume that this is a marvel among the Western factions like the Mercenaries. Despite being chambered in the weaker 9mm instead of the stronger .45 ACP, it's still a relatively good small pistol for those that prefer a SIG-Sauer that shoots 9mm instead of .45 ACP.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium front sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Renowned for its high production quality and good performance, the SG 550 is often referred to as the finest 5.56 mm rifle ever made. It has a side-folding skeletonised buttstock and a lightweight aluminium bipod that folds into grooves in the lower handguard.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550t_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Renowned for its high production quality and good performance, the SG 550 is often referred to as the finest 5.56 mm rifle ever made. It has a side-folding skeletonised buttstock and a lightweight aluminium bipod that folds into grooves in the lower handguard.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Swiss made SIG SG-550 assault rifle. Although it isn't new, it is clear that the previous owner took good care of it: the weapon has been taken apart and put back together with every component fine-tuned for optimum performance, increasing stopping power. The letter "S" has been carved into the stock, along with 16 small notches.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_camot_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Swiss made SIG SG-550 assault rifle. Although it isn't new, it is clear that the previous owner took good care of it: the weapon has been taken apart and put back together with every component fine-tuned for optimum performance, increasing stopping power. The letter "S" has been carved into the stock, along with 16 small notches.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_sniper_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A marksman variant of a popular Swiss-made assault rifle, the SG 550-S constitutes a perfect middle ground between sniper and assault rifles, retaining the strong points of both types of weaponry. On the other hand, it suffers from certain drawbacks such as being somewhat lacking in stopping power and accuracy for a sniper rifle and lack of automatic fire. Still, it remains one of the best top-tier weapon systems available within the Exclusion Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Kahles ZF95 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_strelok_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Swiss made SIG SG-550 assault rifle. Although it isn't new, it is clear that the previous owner took good care of it: the weapon has been taken apart and put back together with every component fine-tuned for optimum performance, increasing stopping power. The letter "S" has been carved into the stock, along with 16 small notches.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] Õ %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_strelokt_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Swiss made SIG SG-550 assault rifle. Although it isn't new, it is clear that the previous owner took good care of it: the weapon has been taken apart and put back together with every component fine-tuned for optimum performance, increasing stopping power. The letter "S" has been carved into the stock, along with 16 small notches.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] Õ %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Steyr Scout sniper rifle is a renowned firearm celebrated for its exceptional accuracy and versatility. Chambered in 5.56x45mm ammunition, this rifle combines precision with portability, making it a favorite among marksmen and military professionals. Its compact design and lightweight construction allow for easy maneuverability in various tactical scenarios, while its robust build ensures durability and reliability in the field. Equipped with advanced optics and a user-friendly interface, the Steyr Scout offers quick target acquisition and superior performance at medium to long-range distances. With its 5.56x45mm chambering, it delivers impressive stopping power and exceptional ballistic performance, making it an ideal choice for both urban and open-field operations.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
        %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-MONSTER suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout_big_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Steyr Scout sniper rifle is a highly regarded firearm known for its precision and adaptability. Chambered in the powerful 7.62x51mm ammunition, this rifle combines formidable stopping power with impressive accuracy, making it a favorite among marksmen and military professionals. Its ergonomic design and lightweight construction allow for easy handling and swift target acquisition, ensuring effectiveness in various tactical situations. The Steyr Scout's robust build guarantees durability and reliability in the harshest environments, making it a trusted choice for snipers and sharpshooters. With its 7.62x51mm chambering, it delivers excellent long-range performance, making it ideal for engaging targets at extended distances with high accuracy and lethal impact.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
        %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svi_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Strayer-Voigt Inc. is a manufacturer of M1911-styled modular pistols, this especially includes the Strayer-Voigt Infinity itself, SVI for short. It is a pistol marketed for competition, so it is rather expensive and rare as it's not available for any army or average arms-bearing citizen. How did this even get in The Zone? No doubt from those flamboyant American mercenaries. The pistol itself has the massive benefit of having its own trademark Strayer-Voigt magazine, which holds 15 rounds. It has also been modified in-house to shoot in 3-burst at a fast rate. Oh and, if none of that makes you happy, the tritium optic fiber will, since it's blue. However, don't expect the same good ol' reliability as the classic 1911.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sw645">
		<text>Smith & Wesson 659</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_wpn_sw645_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Smith & Wesson Model 659 is a 9mm compact pistol manufactured in 1985 and discontinued in 1988, despite so, a lot of folks from the black market are able to obtain it, let alone even make some illegaly even. The S&W 659 is constructed almost entirely from stainless steel and is thus extremely resistant to harsh weather conditions. Since it's very easy to do so, any technician can change the caliber to 9x19, turning it into a S&W Model 645. Overall, good backup pistol if you need less weight and better close quarter combat.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usas12_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Daewoo Precision Industries USAS-12 (Universal Sports Automatic Shotgun 12 gauge) is an automatic shotgun designed for combat manufactured in South Korea by Daewoo Precision Industries in 1980s. How a Korean gun made it into Ukraine is something stalkers would very much like to know. Maybe there's a K2 rifle out there.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally designed for the American market, the USP, Universal Self loading Pistol, is known as an accurate and reliable handgun. U.S. law enforcement and military provided much of the design criteria for the USP. The controls are uniquely American, influenced by famous designs like the Government Model 1911 pistol. All USPs use a fibre-reinforced polymer frame stiffened by stainless steel inserts at areas subject to stress and friction. Incorporating several successful handgun design elements, the USP Compact .45 is a part of the USP family of handguns designed by H&K. Able to withstand extreme punishment and adverse conditions, it is used by several countries' police and special forces units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally designed for the American market, the USP, Universal Self loading Pistol, is known as an accurate and reliable handgun. U.S. law enforcement and military provided much of the design criteria for the USP. The controls are uniquely American, influenced by famous designs like the Government Model 1911 pistol. All USPs use a fibre-reinforced polymer frame stiffened by stainless steel inserts at areas subject to stress and friction. Incorporating several successful handgun design elements, the USP Compact .45 is a part of the USP family of handguns designed by H&K. Able to withstand extreme punishment and adverse conditions, it is used by several countries' police and special forces units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_match_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An enhanced USP by HK with distinct characteristics that make it more attractive to the target shooter. With the O-Ring barrel first seen in the Mark 23, the Match includes compensator that helps reduce the relatively mild kick of the 9x19. The Match also features polygonal rifling, a trigger stop, and fully adjustable rear sight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An enhanced USP by HK with distinct characteristics that make it more attractive to the target shooter. With the O-Ring barrel first seen in the Mark 23, the Match includes compensator that helps reduce the relatively mild kick of the 9x19. The Match also features polygonal rifling, a trigger stop, and fully adjustable rear sight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
<!--	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_compact_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The ultimate classic favourite of every veteran in The Zone be him of any faction. Using a caliber fit for short-range combat, easy to conceal, very reliable and barely any weight for 8 rounds, one can easily use this instead of the average USP.  \n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_tactical_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Considered to be an improvement of the MK23 and USP, it's actually more an improvement of the USP itself in a more compact format. It incorporates an extended, threaded barrel with O-ring, which increases accuracy and reduces recoil as well as allows the integration of a suppressor by default, adjustable micrometer rear sight, with tritium sights for rear & front. All these enhancements, it's clear that this is not a "fresh out of the manufacture" USP Tactical, since the plastic is rather worn & cast while the trigger is tampered with. This could be modifications made in the black market, either way, still a worthy, reliable .45 ACP (or 9mm if you change the caliber) pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
-->	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm parabellum. Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_mod9_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. The Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_xm8_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The XM8 is a lightweight assault rifle system from the late 1990s to early 2000s. The rifle was designed by German small arms manufacturer Heckler & Koch (H&K), and shares design and engineering with their G36 rifle.\n
		The XM8 design was originally part of the Objective Individual Combat Weapon program (OICW), which was developing a "smart" grenade launcher system with an underslung carbine rifle. The system was unable to meet performance and weight requirements and was eventually cancelled. In the aftermath, the two portions of the OICW were separated, resulting in the XM8 and XM25 projects.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, AC11090, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
		
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions Nato 3
-->

	<string id="st_wpn_ar15_freedom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. A highly modified AR15 rifle, usually in service with the veterans of the Freedom. The body kit installed on the weapon allows you to feel confident at any firing range, but at the same time, the weapon is distinguished by a high price due to the use of very expensive components in the kit.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM 556-MONSTER compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. ISG modification of the Swedish AK 5C. A rare weapon in the Zone used by some ISG squads.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The Ak 5C is the modernized version of the original Ak 5 and follows the trend of modular weapons. One of the most significant improvements is the MIL-STD-1913 rail system to which a variety of different optics, lights and sights that can be mounted.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_5c_tik_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The Ak 5C is the modernized version of the original Ak 5 and follows the trend of modular weapons. One of the most significant improvements is the MIL-STD-1913 rail system to which a variety of different optics, lights and sights that can be mounted.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold LCO+D'evo scopes (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO. Steyr AUG A3 in standard rifle configuration. It differs from the A1 model with the presence of four Picatinny rails.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG x4 (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] STEYR UMS compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M1911 was the standard-issue side arm for the US military from 1911 to 1985. An extremely reliable and robust weapon, it's been adopted for military, police and civilian use around the world and remains a very popular firearm to this day. This is a unique model with red stains on dark-beige colour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Coonan .357 Magnum is a peculiar semi-auto gun that uses .357 Magnum done through the chassis of a Colt 1911. This is done by changing the barrel, slide, handle and magazine to accommodate the caliber change. By the looks of it, this came through the Zone thanks to...Some sinister group, how they have acquired it is a mystery, but by the looks of how unkempt, contrasted and slightly broken the gun looks, it could even be an illegal clone of the original Coonan. Sadly, the weapon isn't exactly the best when it comes to accuracy, but the recoil is tolerable (as long as you don't rapid-fire) and the handling is great, one main benefit of using this instead of some other .357 pistols like the Desert Eagle is the conceal carry, weight and better Close Quarters Combat.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_deagle_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Developed by the American company Magnum Research, the Desert Eagle uses a gas operated mechanism commonly found in rifles. This allows the pistol to use much larger caliber bullets than traditional semi-automatic pistols. The disadvantages of this weapon include a considerable size and heavy weight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low), DOCTER Sight III, Deltapoint PRO, Trijicon RMR.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_steppe_eagle_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Developed by the American company Magnum Research, the Desert Eagle uses a gas operated mechanism commonly found in rifles. This allows the pistol to use much larger caliber bullets than traditional semi-automatic pistols. The disadvantages of this weapon include a considerable size and heavy weight. On this barrel, all components are perfectly tuned to achieve the highest accuracy for pistols of this type, thanks to the integrated muzzle compensator, it was possible to significantly reduce recoil. It has a heavily redesigned picatinny rail, thanks to which a wide range of scopes can be mounted. This weapon was brought to the Zone by stalker Logan Williams. Under the guise of a journalist-photographer, he managed to reach the center of Pripyat alone. Currently, his fate is unknown, but there are rumors that he works as an informant for many secret departments on the Exclusion Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The IMI Desert Eagle is a semi-automatic handgun notable for chambering the largest centrefire cartridge of any magazine fed, self-loading pistol and also being the heaviest and blockiest gun of its type. You can use it to bludgeon your enemies to death because of its blockiness and weight. Rumour is that there's a stalker with a crowbar wandering around the Zone with a rechambered version of this gun.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_dhampyr_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A more modernized version of the Desert Eagle, with a build-in compensator and picatinny rails, on frame and slide. Knowing that so, it still has quite a recoil but much lower than any other Desert Eagle, let alone magnum, the slight barrel improvements also improve the accuracy by a bit, and it's possible to insert some scopes. It seems to be of relatively new shape, but looking at the slide and the magazine, it claims to use .50AE and yet it's feeding on .357 Magnum. Without a doubt, it was modified right in The Zone, perhaps by Nimble himself.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical sight.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr"> 		<!-- NOT IN GAMMA ? -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This weapon was brought to the Zone by a stalker named Logan Williams. Disguised as a TIME photographer he managed to single-handedly enter the centre of Pripyat. His current whereabouts are unknown, but he is rumoured to work as an information broker specializing in all matters related to the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DOCTER Sight III.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_sa58_osw_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO. The SA-58 OSW (Operations Specialist Weapon) manufactured by DSA (David Selvaggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL with select-fire that has a fully automatic cyclic rate of 750 rounds/minute. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_nimble_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces. This model has an integrated EOTech sight, which results in slightly lower accuracy, but since this model was aimed for CQC, rate of fire was increased accordingly.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTech sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000e_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces. This model has an integrated EOTech sight, which results in slightly lower accuracy, but since this model was aimed for CQC, rate of fire was increased accordingly.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fn57_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.7x28mm. The Five-seveN is a delayed blowback operated, semi-automatic pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low), DOCTER Sight III, Deltapoint PRO, Trijicon RMR.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28mm compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FN FNP pistol is a series of semi-automatic, polymer framed pistols manufactured in Columbia, South Carolina by FNH USA, a division of Fabrique Nationale de Herstal. Debuted in early 2006, the FNP series weapons are hammer fired weapons utilizing a Browning cam system with an external extractor. The trigger module is housed inside the polymer frame as an individual unit connected to the hammer. The magazine release button is held in place by a retention pin which can be removed to allow the button to be reversed.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FNX line of pistols were introduced in 2009 by FNH USA, a US based subsidiary of the Belgian gun company FN Herstal. Originally developed to the requirements of the US Joint Combat Pistol Program, these pistols are manufactured in US and intended for military, law enforcement and civilian use. All FNX handguns are semi-automatic pistols with double/single action trigger and external hammer. Frame of the every FNX pistol is made from impact resistant polymer, with removable backstraps of different sizes. FNX-45 Tactical is a specialised variant of the basic FNX-45, that features extended threaded barrel and raised sights, to be used with detachable sound suppressor.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FNX Tactical sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium rear sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_nimble">
		<text>G36L "F34R"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]One strange variant of the G36. It appears that an ex-military of the Lithuanian Armed Forces used it, making some personal changes on the go. The gun is similar to the G36K, but much more lightweight, yet despite so has no reduction in accuracy and the recoil is just as bearable. The bolt was personally modified to fire even faster than average. The Handguard is a Lithuanian version of the G36K, which is lighter and has picatinny rails, this allows attaching the M203 compatible grenade launcher on it. It also has KAC ironsights with integrated Tritium sights, the front being much higher in contrast than the rear for better view. The KAC itself includes picatinny rails for scope attachment. A marvel if a bit peculiar of a G36 gun variant.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_g36nimble_rwap">
		<text>G36L "Merc"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36nimble_rwap_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The H&K G-36 was known as the HK-50 project in tge early 1990s. After the cancellation of the G11 and G41 projects, the Bundeswehr was left with outdated G3 rifles. Heckler & Koch was set to develop a new assault rifle for both the German army and for export. The new 5.56x45mm assault rifle was adopted by the Bundeswehr in 1995 and also found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide, including British police and some US police departments. So far, there have been very few complaints about this rifle. It is accurate, reliable and simple in maintenance. A variant of G36c custom made with B&T quad rail handguard with laser sight some fancy merc job.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_descr">
		<text>%c[d_purple]Exotic •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A highly experimental, artefact-powered, super-accurate weapon made by an unknown party in the Zone. Its gunshot is nearly inaudible, because instead of gunpowder, it uses magnets to accelerate its bullet to incredible speeds. Despite the gauss rifle's tremendous firepower, the recoil is insignificant. The accuracy and power of this gun exceeds those of all other small arms.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_purple]Exotic •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A highly experimental, artefact-powered, super-accurate weapon made by an unknown party in the Zone. Its gunshot is nearly inaudible, because instead of gunpowder, it uses magnets to accelerate its bullet to incredible speeds. Despite the gauss rifle's tremendous firepower, the recoil is insignificant. The accuracy and power of this gun exceeds those of all other small arms.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_quest_descr">
		<text>%c[d_purple]Exotic •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A highly experimental, artefact-powered, super-accurate weapon made by an unknown party in the Zone. Its gunshot is nearly inaudible, because instead of gunpowder, it uses magnets to accelerate its bullet to incredible speeds. Despite the gauss rifle's tremendous firepower, the recoil is insignificant. The accuracy and power of this gun exceeds those of all other small arms.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9mm Parabellum. The Glock 17 is a polymer-framed, short recoil-operated, locked-breech semi-automatic pistol. The tactical variant of Glock 17 has some additional futures: integrated Aimtech glock base for Red Dot sights, Pachmayr tactical rubber grip and a threaded barrel.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low), DOCTER Sight III, Deltapoint PRO , Trijicon RMR.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Osprey-9 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_howa20_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. The Type 20 borrows many features from other modern rifles. Is not the originality of the design that is required - but reliability, low price, and compliance with the customer's requirements. It remains a mystery how and in what quantity this rifle came to the participants of a scientific expedition to the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] MARCH Tactical Short Scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KAC QDSS NT-4 5.56x45 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in .45 ACP. The Korth is a high-end pistol; The ROLEX of pistols. This model has a 4" barrel and tritium sights but cannot be fitted with a suppressor.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in .45 ACP. The Korth is a high-end pistol; The ROLEX of pistols. This model has a 6" threaded barrel for a suppressor and high rising sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DOCTER Sight III.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC Black Box compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_kriss_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The KRISS Vector[4] is a series of weapons based upon the parent submachine gun design developed by the American company KRISS USA, formerly Transformational Defense Industries (TDI). They use an unconventional delayed blowback system combined with in-line design to reduce perceived recoil and muzzle climb.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (high), Aimpoint CompM4s, EOTech XPS3-0, EoTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m3_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.56x45 NATO, The L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenariosand is recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using the standard issue SUSAT telescopic sight.This version has been installed with picatinny rails for use with modern sights and optics.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
        %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M320 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Accuracy International Arctic Warfare rifle is a family of bolt-action sniper rifles designed and manufactured by the British company, Accuracy International. It has proved popular as a civilian, police and military rifle since its introduction in the 1980s. The rifles have some features which improve performance in very cold conditions, without impairing operation in less extreme conditions.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1m_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Accuracy International Arctic Warfare rifle is a family of bolt-action sniper rifles designed and manufactured by the British company, Accuracy International. It has proved popular as a civilian, police and military rifle since its introduction in the 1980s. The rifles have some features which improve performance in very cold conditions, without impairing operation in less extreme conditions. L96 AWSM utilises .338 Lapua Magnum.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m24_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A sniper rifle of the US Army, the M24 Sniper Weapon System (SWS) is based on the Remington 700. Fitted with a Leupold 10x40mm scope, the M24 has a stainless steel barrel and an adjustable composite stock made from Kevlar and graphite.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M24 sniper scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_butcher_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Modernized model Colt M4A1 Commando (CQBR) is an assault rifle, designed in the USA on the basis of AR-15 platform for the 5.56x45mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_tac_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Colt M4A1 - an assault rifle (carbine), designed in the USA on the basis of AR-15 platform for 5.56x45mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SR-556 AR-15 style rifle manufactured by U.S. firearms company Sturm, Ruger & Co. The rifle features a "two-stage" piston mechanism as opposed to the semi-direct impingement system of the AR-15. Gas flow is controlled by a four position regulator. Several key parts, such as the short stroke gas piston, gas regulator, and bolt/carrier group are chrome plated. The bolt carrier features an integral lug in place of the AR-15's gas key. In January 2016 Ruger discontinued all SR-556 rifles.\nAccording to rumors, Professor Sakharov should have received 6 small containers with these rifles from foreign partners, but 5 of them were lost during transportation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m60_descr"> <!-- NOT IN GAMMA ? -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The M60, officially the United States Machine Gun, Caliber 7.62 mm, M60, is a family of American general-purpose machine guns firing 7.62x51mm NATO cartridges from a disintegrating belt of M13 links. There are several types of ammunition approved for use in the M60, including ball, tracer, and armor-piercing rounds.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m82_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Barrett M82, in the documentation of the US Armed Forces M107 - American self-loading large-caliber sniper rifle, manufactured by Barrett Firearms Manufacturing and in service with several countries around the world. The automatics of this rifle are based on a butterfly valve. The rifle belongs to the class of "antimaterial", but is more often used as a weapon against enemy infantry.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Shitscope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m98b_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Barrett M98B is a bolt-action sniper rifle chambered in .338 Lapua Mag. Rather than modifying a hunting rifle, Barrett created an original design for the M98B. The M98B features an adjustable stock and cheek pad for comfort, an adjustable trigger for preferable trigger control, a rear monopod and a front bi-pod for stability. Users can further modify the rifle by attaching sights, lights and grips to its rails. The M98B has a simple design making it easy for users to disassemble and clean.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR-25 suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mk23_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]
		Better known as the USSOCOM MARK 23, this is a pistol made by Heckler & Koch for the USSOCOM, a Spec Ops team of the USA. The idea was to make a pistol especially made for Spec Ops, so it has amazing durability, be it harsh environment, water or corrosion, as well as good accuracy and recoil thanks to its polygonal barrel design and instead of the 9mm it uses the more powerful .45 ACP. Despite proving to be quite useful, especially for USSOCOM, it was discontinued due to its unpopularity outside of Spec Ops. In The Zone, this gun is only popular because of the legendarily unpopular ex-Spetnaz stalker, Boleslav "Sishka" Tarchik.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A submachine gun prototype based on the excellent H&K MP5A3 model. Designed as a next generation close quarter combat weapon, it benefits from a higher calibre, rate of fire and accuracy.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EoTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_p90">
		<text>FN P90 TR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities does not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium, bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_p90gamma">
		<text>FN P90 TRG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90gamma_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities does not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium, bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_p90tac">
		<text>FN P90 Tactcal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90tac_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities does not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium, bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta is a rotating cylinder fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and combat. According to certain sources, this model once belonged to Tank, but little is known about him.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_raptr_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RAPTR is an automatic mag–fed shotgun born in the Zone and tailored to the specific needs of that dangerous part of the world. The RAPTR is often called "Bloosuckers Killer" by stalkers. Indeed, its high rate of fire, large magazine and unparalled ergonomics makes it the perfect weapon to kill the fast moving and invisible targets that the bloodsuckers are. Considered mainly as a fancy gun–nut weapon in the past few years, the RAPTR popularity among stalkers started to raise during the recent bloodsuckers nests blooming. It is now considered as one of the finest 12x70 gun in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium rear sight & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hexagon 12K compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_lapua700_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Deer Hunter is a modification of the Remington Model 700 chambered in .338 for precise shooting on very long distances.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] The Deer Hunter .338 kit installed.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] March Tactical scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M700 .338LM compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN40GL compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_black_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN40GL compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_black_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Vortex RAZOR UH-1 EOTech G33.STS magnifier (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A unique model of the SIG-Sauer P220 handgun. Part of a small limited edition made for an unidentified special forces unit. The model benefits from an increased magazine capacity, a high durability steel barrel and an ultra-durable polymer receiver.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig320_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This is an amazing pistol that Nimble found, a very recent addition to the SIG-Sauer pistols, so consider yourself extra-lucky. Chambered in 9mm, one can easily re-chamber it to .45 ACP, just find yourself a technician. It uses a "Strike-Action" mechanism, which should heavily reduce recoil even with .45 ACP. It has unmatched reliability, very good accuracy and perfect recoil. The best pistol you can get, especially .45 ACP if rechambered for such.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Swiss made SIG SG-550 assault rifle. Although it isn't new, it is clear that the previous owner took good care of it: the weapon has been taken apart and put back together with every component fine-tuned for optimum performance, increasing stopping power. The letter "S" has been carved into the stock, along with 16 small notches.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45/7.62 NATO compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An army shotgun designed specifically for assault units and created on the basis of the Franchi SPAS-12. Capable of automatic fire like its predecessor, but provides better recoil compensation thanks to a balanced shock free system. Capable of automatic fire like its predecessor, but provides better recoil compensation thanks to a balanced shock free system.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr25_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SR-25 is an AR-15 rifle scaled up to shoot 7.62x51mm NATO. This rifle also found a favor in US Military. All rifles built on the SR-25 platform share the same basic action. Because of the AR-15 style recoil buffer tube it cannot be fitted with a folding stock. Instead it is fitted with telescoping stock.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium front sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR-25 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_trg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The TRG-42 is not an accurised version of an existing rifle, but was developed from the very beginning as a sniper rifle. Its consistent high accuracy and reliability have made it popular both in long-range competitions and military sniper operations.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FINDOT scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_tac_descr">
        <text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modification of the HK USP Match specially developed for scientists by the personal order of Professor Sakhorov. Chambered in 9mm Parabellum. Designed for use in the "Specialist-Scientist" kit, it has hreading to install a suppressor and comes with an extended, 22 round magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low), DOCTER Sight III, Deltapoint PRO , Trijicon RMR.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC Black Box compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_wa2000_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_blue]NATO  •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Walther WA 2000 is a semi-automatic bullpup sniper rifle produced by the Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen company from 1982 until 1988. It was produced in three different calibers. Production of the rifle was limited and it was shortly stopped because it was too expensive to achieve widespread sales and not robust enough for military use as a sniper rifle. Only 176 were built due to its high cost, making it one of the rarest and most sought production firearms ever made.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] Schmidt & Bender Klassik 2.5-10x scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions WP 1
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_9a91_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x39mm. The 9A91 is a gas operated, rotating bolt weapon, which utilises a long stroke gas piston, located above the barrel, and a rotating bolt with 4 lugs. The receiver is made from steel stampings, the forend and pistol grip are made from polymer. The steel stock folds up and above the receiver when not in use. The flip up rear sight has settings for 100 and 200 metres range, but the relatively short sight base and steep trajectory of the subsonic bullet restricts the 9A-91 to ranges of about 100 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, PSO-1M2-1, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9A-91/VSK-94 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_9a91n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x39mm. The 9A91 is a gas operated, rotating bolt weapon, which utilises a long stroke gas piston, located above the barrel, and a rotating bolt with 4 lugs. The receiver is made from steel stampings, the forend and pistol grip are made from polymer. The steel stock folds up and above the receiver when not in use. The flip up rear sight has settings for 100 and 200 metres range, but the relatively short sight base and steep trajectory of the subsonic bullet restricts the 9A-91 to ranges of about 100 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9A-91/VSK-94 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_adar2_15_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A Russian civilian carbine produced in St. Petersburg and based on the design of the AR-15. As in the case of many other companies that make AR-15s, ADAR doesn’t actually manufacture these rifles but rather assembles them from parts sourced from a variety of manufacturers.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AAC M4-2000 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-47 can be described as a hybrid of previous rifle technology. Mikhail Kalashnikov designed this automatic rifle combining the best features of the American M1 and the German StG44. The Kalashnikov is a gas operated 7.62x39 assault rifle and by far the most prolific small arm of the 2nd half of the 20th century. It had been and still is, in more or less modified form, manufactured in dozens of countries and has been used in hundreds of conflicts since its introduction.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_alt_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_eot_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake. This particular model has an integrated EOTech holosight and a 45 round magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTech sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.45x39mm. The AK-74 is an ssault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_old_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake. This particular variant was assembled a long time ago.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_old_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range. This model seems to be very old.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_n1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.45x39mm. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_snag_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range. This special variant has a 45 round RPK magazine, an integrated Kobra sight and an integrated suppressor.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-1S-03 Kobra (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-104 is a 7.62x39mm carbine version of the AK-103 rifle. It features a shortened barrel that makes it a middle ground between a full rifle and the more compact AKS-74U. The rifle's receiver is made of stamped steel; the magazine is made out of reinforced fibreglass and the stock is made of hollow plastic, making it lighter, more durable, and allowing a field kit to be stored inside of it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AKM is a 7.62x39mm assault rifle designed by Mikhail Kalashnikov. It is an improved version of the AK-47 rifle and was developed in the 1950's. Introduced to the Red Army in 1959, the AKM is the most ubiquitous variant of the AK series of firearms and it has found widespread use with the former Warsaw Pact states and its many African and Asian allies. The production of AKM rifles was carried out at the Tula Arsenal and Izhevsk Mechanical Works.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x39mm. The AKM is the most ubiquitous variant of the AK series of firearms and it has found widespread use with the former Warsaw Pact states and its many African and Asian allies.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_descr">  <!-- wpn_akms_alt inherits  -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the AKM, equipped with an under-folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. The metal stock of the AKMS is somewhat different from the folding stock of the previous AK-47 model as it has a modified locking mechanism, which locks both support arms of the AKMS stock instead of just one.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the AKM, equipped with an under-folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. The metal stock of the AKMS is somewhat different from the folding stock of the previous AK-47 model as it has a modified locking mechanism, which locks both support arms of the AKMS stock instead of just one.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aks_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the AK-47, equipped with an under folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. It was designed for use inside armoured vehicles and by paratroopers.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the AK-47, equipped with an under folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. It was designed for use inside armoured vehicles and by paratroopers.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_new_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of the AK-47, equipped with an under folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. It was designed for use inside armoured vehicles and by paratroopers.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_bizon_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This submachine gun was developed during the early 1990s, first appearing to the public in 1993. Influenced by the Calico submachine guns, This SMG combined high capacity helical magazine with more conventional appearance and layout. The Bizon is built on shortened AKS-74 receivers, made from stamped steel. It featured a simple blowback action, hammer fired from closed bolt. Sights are similar to ones found on the AKS-74U.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1P76, EKP 1S-03 Kobra, EKP 8-02, OKP-07 (dovetail mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight & Tactical laser aiming module.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A double-barrelled shotgun with shortened barrels. Lighter and more compact, effective at close range. Needing a cheap, short range weapon that's effective and lethal, many rookie stalkers resort to sawing off the buttstock and barrel on the easily acquired TOZ 66. This makes the shotgun quick to wield, but at the cost of range and accuracy.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A powerful weapon that every stalker can afford, TOZ 66 is a close range firearm possessing both reliability and effectiveness. However, being large and unwieldy, many stalkers prefer to spend their hard-earned rubles on a modern handgun instead.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_cz52_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The CZ 52 (also known by the Czechoslovak military designations vz. 52, for (vz. - vzor = model) "model of 1952", and CZ 482) is a semi-automatic pistol designed by two brothers, Jan and Jaroslav Kratochvil, in the early 1950s for the Czechoslovak military. Around 200,000 vz. 52s were made by Ceska Zbrojovka in Strakonice from 1952 to 1954. Before standardizing on the 7.62x25mm vz. 52, the Czechoslovak military used several domestic and foreign pistol models in three different calibers.</text>
	</string>
<!-- 
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_descr"> NOT USED ANYMORE ? 
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_black]The Fort-17 pistol is the latest development of the Ukrainian state owned FORT factory. It is a polymer framed modification of the earlier Fort-12 pistol, and all the mechanisms and properties are almost identical between the two pistols. However, the Fort-17 is lighter than its predecessor and features a removable grip backstrap, which can be had in various sizes, to adapt the pistol for a particular shooter.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string> 
-->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fort12_descr">	<!-- wpn_fort in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Fort-12 is an attempt for recently-independent Ukraine (from August 1991) to create its own police pistol to replace the Soviet-era Makarov PM, while still using the same 9x18 caliber. Designed in 1995 and developed in 1998 by Ukrainian firearms designer RPC Fort, this is a formidable pistol considered to be an upgrade of the PM itself. Although it may have reliability issues, especially due to the lack of the safe decocking facility, it compensates for the accuracy, magazine and ergonomics. This model comes with a threaded barrel, allowing it to equip silencers by default.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fort17_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Fort-17 is an improvement of the Fort-12 by replacing the frame from steel to polymer, which decreases weight, although the recoil might be just a little bit worse. Comes with magazines size 13 by default instead of 12 or 13. It also has a removable grip backstrap, which can improve ergonomics.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fort500_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Fort-500 smoothbore rifle was developed by the Fort NGO of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine in the late 1990s, and was intended to arm the staff of the Ministry of Internal Affairs and security services of Ukraine. At present, the FORT-500 rifle in limited quantities is in service with the special units of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine, and is also sold to citizens of this country in a hunting variant.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]OTs-02 "Kiparis" (Cypress) is a sub-machine gun, developed in 1972 by order of the Ministry of Defence of the USSR by weapon designers from TsKIB COO of Tula. The layout is based on the Czechoslovak sub-machine gun Scorpion Vz.61 (1961 variant). The OTs-02 "Kiparis" automatic mechanism is powered by a free bolt recoil. Shots are fired from closed bolt, which increases the accuracy of fire. To increase stability of the weapon, a folding stock is used, which in the compact position is folded on top of the receiver. In the Zone, this weapon is not uncommon and usually used by bandits and loners who can't afford a better weapon.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- <string id="st_wpn_mp133_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP-133 shotgun uses traditional pump action with sliding forend that has dual action bars. Locking is achieved by a tilting locking piece, installed in the bolt and engages the notch in the barrel extension when in battery. Feed is from tubular underbarrel magazine that holds 4 rounds, though capacity can be enhanced by installing magazine extension tubes.</text>
	</string> NOT USED ANYMORE ? -->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP-133 shotgun is a 12 gauge, traditional pump action shotgun with an installed five shell tube.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A basic version of the Mosin-Nagant with slightly worn interiors. The M1891/30 was produced for standard issue to all Soviet infantry from 1930 to 1945. It was extremely successful in World War II as a sniper rifle when it was equipped with a 4x PE or a 3.5x PU scope.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PB (Pistolet Besshumnyj or Silent Pistol), also known in the Soviet army as 6P9, has been developed in 1967 for Spetsnaz units of the Soviet Army, as well as for KGB operatives. The pistol is based on a modified Makarov PM pistol and features an unique integral two part suppressor. Issued into service in 1967, the PB (GRAU index 6P9) is a Soviet silenced pistol based on the Makarov PM. It was intended for use by the KGB and army reconnaissance groups. The front part of the suppressor is detachable, so that the pistol can be broken down into two parts for convenient carry. The PB's integral suppressor also reduces the bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6P9 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PB (Pistolet Besshumnyj or Silent Pistol), also known in the Soviet army as 6P9, has been developed in 1967 for Spetsnaz units of the Soviet Army, as well as for KGB operatives. The pistol is based on a modified Makarov PM pistol and features an unique integral two part suppressor. Issued into service in 1967, the PB (GRAU index 6P9) is a Soviet silenced pistol based on the Makarov PM. It was intended for use by the KGB and army reconnaissance groups. The front part of the suppressor is detachable, so that the pistol can be broken down into two parts for convenient carry. The PB's integral suppressor also reduces the bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6P9 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PB is a modified Makarov PM pistol and features a unique integral two part suppressor. The PB's integral suppressor reduces the bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6P9 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PB is a modified Makarov PM pistol and features a unique integral two part suppressor. The PB's integral suppressor reduces the bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6P9 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_actor_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An ancient PM given to Degtyarev as a reward for "Successful execution of highly dangerous state orders, as well as valour and courage shown in the line of duty".</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size. In 1951, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy, and reasonable stopping power.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x18mm. This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_actor_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A semi-mythical PM with extended barrel and suppressor mount threading. Some claim it was a limited series manufactured in Bulgaria.oothers insist on DDR. Some are even prone to think of it as a handcrafted upgrade. No living soul can tell how did it end up in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Customized version of Makarov PM with longer threaded barrel for use with PMM suppressor.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PMM compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The most widely known variant, the Makarov PMM was a redesign of the original gun. In 1990 a group of engineers reworked the original Makarov, primarily by increasing the load for the cartridge. The result is 25% more gas pressure increasing in muzzle velocity. The PMM magazine holds 12 rounds, compared to the PM's 8 rounds.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x18mm. The most widely known variant, the Makarov PMM was a redesign of the original gun. The PMM magazine holds 12 rounds, compared to the PM's 8 rounds.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PMM compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ppk_descr">  <!-- wpn_pm_custom in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Walther PPK (Polizeipistole Kurz) is a semi-automatic pistol developed by the German arms manufacturer, Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen, in 1935 and still today. It is considered to be a classic pistol from the West, used extensively worldwide. It's no surprise it got to The Zone itself, by either enthusiasts, the Black Market or even ex-policemen. Very popular among rookies, especially those that go around arrogantly saying they are "Sharpshooters". Of important note, it has been modified to shoot 9x18 Makarov instead of the default and rare .32 ACP.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A major infantry weapon of the Soviet armed forces during World War II, the PPSh-41 was a durable, low-maintenance weapon made of cheap, easily-obtained components. They utilise 7.62x25mm cartridge.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rpd_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RPD (Degtyaryov hand-held machine gun) is a light machine gun developed in the Soviet Union by Vasily Degtyaryov for the intermediate 7.62x39mm M43 cartridge.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SKS is one of the first weapons chambered for the 7.62x39mm round. Replaced in Soviet front-line service by the AK-47 in the early 1950s, it remained in second-line service for decades and is still used as a ceremonial arm today.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_b_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SKS is one of the first weapons chambered in 7.62x39mm. Replaced in the Soviet front-line service by the AK-47 in the early 1950s, it remained in second-line service for decades and is still used as a ceremonial arm today.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_molot_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Molot OP-SKS Carbine chambered in 7.62x39mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SVT-40 is a surplus semi-automatic rifle chambered in the 7.62x54mmR round. It saw widespread use in the Red Army and Wehrmacht during WWII.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_decor_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Intended for professional and amateur hunting the TOZ-34 is an over/under shotgun. Though lacking in capacity, only 2 rounds, it compares well with high-grade shotguns due to its high accuracy of hits. The TOZ 34 was designed by N. I. Korovyakov and V. P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable in price, with high damage output and its ability to unload both rounds instantly make it a popular weapon among rookies on the outskirts of the Zone. Especially useful against mutants thanks to its accuracy and stopping power.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Intended for professional and amateur hunting the TOZ-34 is an over/under shotgun. Though lacking in capacity, only 2 rounds, it compares well with high-grade shotguns due to its high accuracy of hits. The TOZ 34 was designed by N. I. Korovyakov and V. P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable in price, with high damage output and its ability to unload both rounds instantly make it a popular weapon among rookies on the outskirts of the Zone. Especially useful against mutants thanks to its accuracy and stopping power.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_bull_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Hand made modification of TOZ-34 that uses only specially made "Bull" ammunition that could probably stop a tank. Modifications are mostly related to the strength of the gun, and at a first glance, it looks simply like a decorated TOZ-34. But when you take a closer look, you can see that barrel is made from a unique metal, betraying its non-standard origin, and the stock is also made from some type of carbon fibre, inscribed with the letter "F". It's hard to tell who made it and how it ended up in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632 (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_mark4_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Intended for professional and amateur hunting the TOZ-34 is an over/under shotgun. Though lacking in capacity, only 2 rounds, it compares well with high-grade shotguns due to its high accuracy of hits. The TOZ 34 was designed by N. I. Korovyakov and V. P. Ochnev in 1965. Affordable in price, with high damage output and its ability to unload both rounds instantly make it a popular weapon among rookies on the outskirts of the Zone. Especially useful against mutants thanks to its accuracy and stopping power. This model has a Leupold Mark 4 scope attached to it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_mark4_23_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A powerful weapon that was heavily modified to support 23x75 ammo. The TOZ 34 is a long range firearm possessing both reliability and effectiveness. This peculiar TOZ-34 was modified according to the Zone's needs by supporting a larger, more efficient rounds that the classic 12ga and given a scope, and tighter choke to enable safe distance elimination of large mutants. This earned quite a reputation among stalkers as an efficient gun to hunt large mutants like Chimeras.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632 (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]TOZ-34 (custom sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Intended for professional and amateur hunting the TOZ-34 is a over/under shotgun. Modifications made to this gun by removing much of the barrel and the stock makes this shotgun more compact and easier to carry. Popular among rookies and bandits as they can hide it easily in their trench coats.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz106_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The TOZ-106 is a small, lightweight bolt-action shotgun produced and sold by Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod.This is a compact version of Soviet MTs 20-01 hunting shotgun. It features a metal stock that folds underneath the weapon in order to make it more compact, and a pistol grip. The rest of the stock is wooden. This shotgun was officially marketed as a hunting weapon, but became popular in the zone among rookie loners and bandits.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz106_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The TOZ-106 is a small, lightweight bolt-action shotgun produced and sold by Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod.This is a compact version of Soviet MTs 20-01 hunting shotgun with a Mosin stock. This shotgun was officially marketed as a hunting weapon, but became popular in the zone among rookie loners and bandits.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights for Picatinny & Dovetail mount (check details).</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The TOZ-194 is a 12 Gauge, pump action shotgun manufactured by the Tula Arms Plant. Designed during the last years of the Soviet Union, the manufacture of this firearm has started after its collapse, and since then it has gained a certain popularity within civilian shooters in Russia and in Europe and is reported to be in use with some Russian Security forces.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="wpn_tt33_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The TT-33 is a Russian 7.62x25mm pistol. It was developed in the early 1930s by Fedor Tokarev as a service pistol for the Soviet military to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver. Many communist or Soviet bloc countries made a variation of the TT-33 pistol, until it was eventually replaced by 9x18mm Makarov PM in 1952. Production of the TT-33 in the USSR ended in 1954.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_type63_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Type 63, often incorrectly referred to as Type 68 by Western sources, is a Chinese-designed rifle with a resemblance to the SKS. However, the weapon uses a rotating bolt working system from the AK-47 rifle instead of the tilting bolt system of the SKS.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally chambered for .32 ACP when adopted by the Czechoslovak Army in 1961, mass production of the Skorpion vz. 68 never took place. Even so, a large number of pre-production vz. 68 models made their way into the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •··\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally chambered for .32 ACP when adopted by the Czechoslovak Army in 1961, mass production of the Skorpion vz. 68 never took place. Even so, a large number of pre-production vz. 68 models made their way into the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions WP 2
-->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A key improvement of the AN-94 over the AK-74 is the introduction of the additional 2-rounds burst mode. Nikonov design delays the force of recoil until the fired rounds have left the barrel, which along with a unique 1800 rpm two-shot burst function increases body armour piercing capabilities of this firearm. Used by Spetsnaz operators as well as Duty members to take out armoured targets at relatively long ranges.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M , 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A key improvement of the AN-94 over the AK-74 is the introduction of the additional 2-rounds burst mode. Nikonov design delays the force of recoil until the fired rounds have left the barrel, which along with a unique 1800 rpm two-shot burst function increases body armour piercing capabilities of this firearm. Used by Spetsnaz operators as well as Duty members to take out armoured targets at relatively long ranges.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M , 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The key feature of the AN-94 is a unique 1800 rpm two-shot burst function that increases the body armour piercing capabilities of this rifle. Used by Spetsnaz operators as well as Duty members to take out armoured targets at relatively long ranges.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Based on previous AK rifles in internal design and layout, the AEK-971 is also equipped with a recoil-balancing mechanism, resulting in more controllable automatic fire. Small batches of this rifle were manufactured for the Russian MVD.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-12 assault rifle is the newest rifle intended to replace older Kalashnikov AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles for domestic use, as well as for export. The rifle is a gas operated, selective fire rifle using traditional "Kalashnikov type" action with long stroke gas piston and rotary bolt locking. The bolt group is noticeably lightened to decrease recoil and improve accuracy in automatic fire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1_descr">
        <text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The version of the AK-12 presented to the public in 2016. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It differs quite significantly in appearance and in the design of a number of important units from the previous version of the AK-12 shown in 2015.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-105 is a 5.45x39mm carbine version of the AK-74M rifle. The AK-105 is supplementing AKS-74U carbines in Russian Army service. Ideal for CQC (close quarters combat), it's not intended for long range combat. The rifle's reiver is made of stamped steel; the magazine is made out of reinforced fibreglass and the stock is made of hollow plastic, making it lighter, more durable, and allowing a field kit to be stored inside of it.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraged with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_alt_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_beard_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Lightweight and tailored to the harsh conditions of the Zone. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It does not have mounts for a grenade launcher. It is made at Skadovsk and Yanov Station, from where it disperses throughout the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights & Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_duty_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.45x39mm. The AK-74M assault rifle features a new foldable synthetic stock with a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_pk-a_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation. This model has a PK-A sight installed on the MTK-83 optical mount.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PK-A red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.45x39mm. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range. This special variant has a 45 round RPK magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSB-4 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-103 assault rifle is a derivative of the AK-74M chambered for 7.62x39mm, same as the AKM and AK-47. The AK-103 can be fitted with a variety of sights including: laser, night vision, and telescopic sights, plus a suppressor and the GP-25 grenade launcher. It uses plastic components where ever possible instead of wood or metal to reduce weight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_camo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AK-103 assault rifle is a derivative of the AK-74M chambered for 7.62x39mm, same as the AKM and AK-47. The AK-103 can be fitted with a variety of sights including: laser, night vision, and telescopic sights, plus a suppressor and the GP-25 grenade launcher. It uses plastic components where ever possible instead of wood or metal to reduce weight.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_shakal_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A very rare variant of the AK-105. It is found mainly among the veterans of the Duty group. Due to the presence of several sighting devices, it is ideal for combat both at close and medium-long distances.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG x4 & Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_sp_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2] A modification based on the AK-105. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. A very balanced weapon with low recoil, good accuracy and high wear resistance.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1PN93-1, 1PN93-4, PSO-1-M, 1P29 "Tulip", 1P78, 1P29 "Tulpan".\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Deltapoint Pro Red Dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_swamp_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A very rare variant of the AK-105 chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. It is found mainly among the veterans of the Clear Sky group. Due to the presence of several sighting devices, it is ideal for combat both at close and medium-long distances.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Elcan SpecterDr Scope & Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. The Stechkin automatic pistol was originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev but was changed to the 9x18mm calibre used in the new Makarov pistol, as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, both the Makarov and Stechkin were introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the ageing TT-33.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] APS compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol chambered in 9x18mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
		<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_apsabigo_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x18mm. The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] APB compatible suppressor.\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_alt_23_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A powerful weapon that was heavily modified to support 23x75 ammo. The TOZ 66 is a close range firearm possessing both reliability and effectiveness. This peculiar TOZ-66 was modified according to the Zone's needs by supporting larger, more efficient rounds that the classic 12ga. This earned quite a reputation among stalkers as an efficient gun to hunt large mutants like Chimeras.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The CZ-75 was developed in the Czech Republic by the Koucky brothers. This semi-automatic pistol first appeared in 1975, entered production in 1976 and was intended for the export market. The CZ-75 accumulated the best features from many preceding designs and the resulting pistol was aesthetically attractive, comfortable to handle, shoot, accurate and reliable in operation. Made by CZ arms in various versions and modifications, the CZ-75 was also widely copied and cloned.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_auto_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The CZ-75 was developed in the Czech Republic by the Koucky brothers. This semi-automatic pistol first appeared in 1975, entered production in 1976 and was intended for the export market. The CZ-75 accumulated the best features from many preceding designs and the resulting pistol was aesthetically attractive, comfortable to handle, shoot, accurate and reliable in operation. Made by CZ arms in various versions and modifications, the CZ-75 was also widely copied and cloned. The CZ-75 Auto is a 1995 model, boasting of a fully automatic fire mode and a longer barrel.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_snag">
		<text>Fort-21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort_snag_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Fort-21.01 is a copy of the Jericho 941 manufactured by "RPC Fort", made after making a contract with "Israel Military Industries" in September 2009. Considering its relatively "new" status, especially in The Zone, it is a rather rare pistol, hence the price. It is modeled upon the CZ-75, in which case both can share their respective 16-rounds magazines. It uses 9x19 caliber instead of 9x18 unlike its older brothers, the Fort-12 and Fort-17.\n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The GSh-18 is a 9x19mm semi-automatic pistol developed in the early 1990s at the KBP Instrument Design Bureau in Tula. The pistol's name is derived from its designers - Gryazev and Shipunow, and the number 18 denotes the magazine capacity. The GSh-18 is a recoil-operated, locked breech pistol. The weapon has an unusual cam-rotated barrel with 10 locking lugs. The GSh-18 is striker fired and features a pre-set trigger that pre-cocks the pistol when the slide recoils after firing a shot, the striker firing pin is then fully cocked by pulling the trigger back to the rear. With the 7N21 and 7N31 armour-piercing bullets, it can pierce 8mm of steel at 20 metres.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The GSh-18 is a 9x19mm semi-automatic pistol developed in the early 1990s at the KBP Instrument Design Bureau in Tula. The pistol's name is derived from its designers - Gryazev and Shipunow, and the number 18 denotes the magazine capacity. The GSh-18 is a recoil-operated, locked breech pistol. The weapon has an unusual cam-rotated barrel with 10 locking lugs. The GSh-18 is striker fired and features a pre-set trigger that pre-cocks the pistol when the slide recoils after firing a shot, the striker firing pin is then fully cocked by pulling the trigger back to the rear. With the 7N21 and 7N31 armour-piercing bullets, it can pierce 8mm of steel at 20 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Automatic grenade launcher system, 70% unified with automatic machines of the AKS-74U type (the main differences are the 9x39 mm caliber, the bull-pap layout scheme and wider opportunities for modernization). Designed for arming rapid response units. It is highly appreciated by the military and stalkers for the ability to reliably hit an enemy protected by a bulletproof vest or located in a shelter. It can be assembled in 4 different configurations, depending on the combat mission.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PO4x34 scope.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Automatic grenade launcher system, 70% unified with automatic machines of the AKS-74U type (the main differences are the 9x39 mm caliber, the bull-pap layout scheme and wider opportunities for modernization). Designed for arming rapid response units. It is highly appreciated by the military and stalkers for the ability to reliably hit an enemy protected by a bulletproof vest or located in a shelter. It can be assembled in 4 different configurations, depending on the combat mission.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PO4x34 scope.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Special carbine, 23 mm - Soviet multifunctional police pump-action shotgun. Having a caliber of more than 20mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Special carbine, 23 mm. This modification of the KS-23 has a short 510mm barrel installed instead of the standard 700mm barrel.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Shortened version of KS-23 with removable metal stock.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Shortened version of the KS-23 with mounted Trijicon RMR reflex sight. This version has been threaded for a sound suppressor that can be found somewere in the southern locations of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Trijicon RMR (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Swine 23 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Modification of KS-23, developed for the needs of the scientific staff located in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PU scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP-153 self-loading shotgun was the first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. It was developed along with the pump action MP-133 shotgun and shares many parts and assemblies with it. The MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin, and is widely used to hunt various games in Russia. It is also sold for export, it is known as Remington "Spartan" SPR-453 autoloader in US. MP-153 shotguns are known for solid but somewhat heavy construction and reliability.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A customized version of the MP-153 12 gauge shotgun. Capable of semi-automatic fire like its predecessor, but provides better recoil compensation thanks to the quite effective muzzle brake. It also has Picatinny rail which allows to use reflex and holographic sights and ability to use sound suppressor.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights for Picatinny rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Salvo 12 compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas_descr">   <!-- NOT IN GAMMA ? -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP-153 is a 12 gauge, self-loading, semi-auto shotgun with an installed five shell tube.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]OTs-33 "Pernach" (Russian for multivaned mace) is a recent entry into the small class of Russian automatic pistols. The OTs-33 is a blowback-operated weapon firing the 9x18mm Makarov pistol cartridge in automatic and semi-automatic mode. The Pernach was developed in 1995 to replace the Stechkin APS pistol in special paramilitary units. Designed in 1995 by Igor Stechkin at the TSKIB SOO, Central Design Bureau for Sporting and Hunting arms, Tula, Russia, the same designer who developed the APS.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] APS compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PP-2000 is the latest development of the Instrument Design Bureau (KBP) from Tula, Russia. First displayed to the public in 2004, the patent for its layout has been filed in 2001 and was issued in 2003. The niche for the PP-2000 is a personal defence weapon for non-infantry military personnel, as well as close combat weapon for special forces and special law enforcement teams. As such, it is a compact weapon with few parts for reliability, simplified maintenance and low cost. Best suited for close combat.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PP-2000 is the latest development of the Instrument Design Bureau (KBP) from Tula, Russia. First displayed to the public in 2004, the patent for its layout has been filed in 2001 and was issued in 2003. The niche for the PP-2000 is a personal defence weapon for non-infantry military personnel, as well as close combat weapon for special forces and special law enforcement teams. As such, it is a compact weapon with few parts for reliability, simplified maintenance and low cost. Best suited for close combat.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rg6_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RG-6 (index 6G30) was in development between 1993 and 1994 by the TSKIB SOO. The new stand-alone, rapid-firing multi-shot launcher was required to increase the firepower of the infantry during the urban combat, due to recent small scale conflicts, such as the Chechen Wars. The RG-6 entered limited production by mid-1990s and is now in use by various elements of the Russian Army and special forces, as well as by special forces in MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry). The RG-6 is designed to fire all standard 40mm caseless grenades, available for general issue underbarrel launchers, such as GP-25 and GP-30. These rounds include VOG-25 fragmentation grenade, VOG-25P bouncing fragmentation grenade and "Gvozd" (Nail) nonlethal tear gas grenade for riot control. The drum is also front-loaded. Widely used for rapid suppression of enemy firing positions and, when in the open, attacking defended fixed targets or fighting particularly tough mutants.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RPK is a Soviet light machine gun, developed by Mikhail Kalashnikov in 1961 based on the Kalashnikov assault rifle. Created as part of Soviet efforts to standardise the armoury of the Red Army, the RPK replaced the RPD and is still in use to present day.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RPK (Ruchnoy Pulemyot Kalashnikova or Kalashnikov hand-held machine gun) is a 5.45x45mm light machine gun, developed by Mikhail Kalashnikov in the late 1950s. It was created as part of a program designed to standardise the small arms inventory of the Red Army, where it replaced the 7.62x39mm RPD light machine gun. Today, the RPK continues to be used by the armed forces of countries of the former Soviet Union and certain African and Asian nations. The Polish Army adopted the weapon in 1974, where it is used in airborne assault, reconnaissance and special operations units. The RPK was also manufactured under license in Bulgaria and Romania.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M , 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Saiga-12 is a Kalashnikov pattern, 12 gauge combat shotgun, manufactured by Izhmash. The Saiga-12 is recognizable by its Kalashnikov design with the large lever safety on the right side of the receiver, the optic mounting rail on the left and the large top mounted dust cover held in place by the rear of the recoil spring assembly. Earning respect in the Zone for its lethality, it is intended for engaging targets at short range (50 metres or less) or in confined spaces.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Saiga-12 "Nerd" is evidence of Professorâ€™s Sakhorov concern for his collegues. Chambered in 12 gauge. This Saiga was purchased specifically for his personnel and is used in negotiations with especially dangerous mutants about the transfer of their organs as a gift to science. Experienced hunters look with considerable envy at the "nerds" armed with this shotgun.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1P76, EKP-8-02 Kobra, EKP 1S-03 Kobra, OKP-07 (dovetail mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hexagon 12K compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_tac_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Molot OP-SKS Carbine chambered in 7.62x39mm. The tactical version offers a four-rail mount for installing various sights, as well as the ability to install a suppressor. A lighter trigger was installed on this model which significantly increased the rate of fire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally intended for designated marksmen in every basic Soviet infantry unit, the Dragunov SVD was not designed for specialised sniper teams. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_custom_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Originally intended for designated marksmen in every basic Soviet infantry unit, the Dragunov SVD was not designed for specialised sniper teams. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x54mmR. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 meters.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various scopes for Warsaw pact mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP compatible suppressor (after modification).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The OTs-03 SVU is a rare, compact version of the SVD sniper rifle, created for use by the airborne infantry, but later employed mainly by the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main difference between it and the SVD is it's compact size and thus improved handling, thanks to a bullpup configuration and shortened barrel, making it sought after by stalkers in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SVU-Type compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_val_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AS Val is widely used by Russian Army recon units, as well as by MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry) and FSB (Federal Security Bureau) Special Forces. The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. The receiver is machined from steel forging for improved strength. It has a standard side-mounted rail for optical, night vision or red dot scopes but has no provision for mounting a bayonet or a grenade launcher. The integral suppressor could be easily detached for maintenance, repair, or compact storage, but the rifle should not be fired with the suppressor removed due to safety and reliability issues.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AS Val is widely used by Russian Army recon units, as well as by MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry) and FSB (Federal Security Bureau) Special Forces. The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. The receiver is machined from steel forging for improved strength. It has a standard side-mounted rail for optical, night vision or red dot scopes but has no provision for mounting a bayonet or a grenade launcher. The integral suppressor could be easily detached for maintenance, repair, or compact storage, but the rifle should not be fired with the suppressor removed due to safety and reliability issues.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_val_tac_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x39mm.  The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. It has a dovetail mount for various standard dovetail sights.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS/VAL compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Vepr-12 is a multi-purpose semi-automatic shotgun, created by Molot-Oruzhie Ltd. It is patterned after Kalashnikov rifles, and built on the heavy RPK light machine gun receiver. Like the Kalashnikov rifle, it is a rotating bolt, gas operated gun that feeds from a 10 round magazine.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vihr_descr">			<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SR-3 "Vikhr" ("Whirlwind") compact assault rifle was developed in CNIITochMash and manufactured by Tula Arms Plant. Initially known as "MA" (Malogabaritnyj Avtomat - small size assault rifle), it was based on the suppressed 9x39mm AS-Val assault rifle, and intended for concealed carry by special VIP protection teams and State Security operatives, SR3M Vikhr is result of combining the qualities of SR-3, AS VAL and VSS Vintorez. SR-3M also has a larger capacity of 30 rounds, which also provides more reliable feeding during automatic fire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, PSO-1M2-1, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR-3M compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vihrn_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SR-3 "Vikhr" ("Whirlwind") compact assault rifle was developed in CNIITochMash and manufactured by Tula Arms Plant. Initially known as "MA" (Malogabaritnyj Avtomat - small size assault rifle), it was based on the suppressed 9x39mm AS-Val assault rifle, and intended for concealed carry by special VIP protection teams and State Security operatives, SR3M Vikhr is result of combining the qualities of SR-3, AS VAL and VSS Vintorez. SR-3M also has a larger capacity of 30 rounds, which also provides more reliable feeding during automatic fire.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR-3M compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Designed at TsNIITochMash by Peter Serdyukov and his team, the new rifle was intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD. The VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm bullets. The effective range of the VSS is limited to 300-400 metres. Standard sighting equipment consists of side rail on the receiver, which usually accommodates the 4x  PSO-1M2-1 scope. Any other scope or night vision sight can be mounted on the appropriate mount. Backup iron sights consist of tangent rear and blade front. The rear sight is graduated for up to 400 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M2-1, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_1pn93_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Designed at TsNIITochMash by Peter Serdyukov and his team, the new rifle was intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD. The VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm bullets. The effective range of the VSS is limited to 300-400 metres. Standard sighting equipment consists of side rail on the receiver, which usually accommodates the 4x  PSO-1M2-1 scope. Any other scope or night vision sight can be mounted on the appropriate mount. Backup iron sights consist of tangent rear and blade front. The rear sight is graduated for up to 400 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1PN93 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_n1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x39mm. The VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities and the great lethality. It has a dovetail mount for various standard dovetail sights. The effective range of the VSS is limited to 300-400 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A special variant of the famous VSS sniper rifle. This model has been extensively customised. Its internal mechanism has been replaced with a better one, which results in increased muzzle velocity and accuracy. It has an effective range of up to 600 metres.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS/VAL compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
<!--NOT USED ANYMORE
	<string id="st_wpn_vityaz_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A variant of PP-19 with 30-round magazine chambered for 9x19mm, designed in 2004. It is used by patrol groups, Russian traffic police, Russian security police, and by units of the MVD.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
-->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vityaznew_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A 9x19mm Parabellum submachine gun developed from the PP-19 Bizon. Based on the AK-74 and even sharing most of its parts, it is considered to be the "MP5 of the Russian Federation".\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, C-MORE Tactical Sight, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94_descr">		<!-- Not used since 0.9.1 -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The VSK-94 is a 9x39mm suppressed sniper rifle developed by the Russian KBP Instrument Design Bureau as a low-cost alternative to the VSS rifle. The rifle is based on the 9A-91 carbine. The VSK-94 was designed to accurately engage unarmoured targets at ranges up to 400m.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M2-1, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9A-91/VSK-94 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94n_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw ••·\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The VSK-94 is a 9x39mm suppressed sniper rifle developed by the Russian KBP Instrument Design Bureau as a low-cost alternative to the VSS rifle. The rifle is based on the 9A-91 carbine. The VSK-94 was designed to accurately engage unarmoured targets at ranges up to 400m.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9A-91/VSK-94 compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	Blackmarket Weapon Descriptions WP 3
-->
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_custom_descr">
        <text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Modified version of AK-12 2012. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. Used by the Monolithh faction. It has three firing modes: Automatic, Single, and Three rounds burst.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_mono_kit_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A further modified version of AK-12 Monolith. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It has three firing modes: Automatic, Single, and Three rounds burst. Thanks to the new trigger group, it is a more advanced and powerful weapon than the original with an increased rate of fire and improved balancing. This upgrade is irreversible.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG x4 (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP30 "Guard" compatible grenade launcher.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n %c[ui_gray_2]An advanced version of the AK-74M developed by Rifle Dynamics. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modification of the AK-74. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It differs from the standard version by the installed body kit, which includes a tactical grip, a forend with picatinny rails and a folding telescopic buttstock, which significantly improves ergonomics of the gun. The kit also includes a laser targeting device, a tactical flashlight and an adapter mount for sighting devices.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An advanced version of the AK-74M developed by Rifle Dynamics. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_m1_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]An advanced version of the AK-74M developed by Rifle Dynamics. Chambered in 5.45x39mm. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
  	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_alfa_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x39mm. Customized version of the AK-104 assault rifle.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
  	</string>
	
  	<string id="st_wpn_akm_alfa_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x39mm and developed in Israel by Command Arms & Acessories (CAA), the AK-Alfa assault rifle was first presented to the public in 2016. This weapon is marketed under two brands - "Kalashnikov USA" and "Kalashnikov Israel". Apparently, this weapon got into the Zone with the ISG faction. The AK-Alpha assault rifle is an attempt to improve the ergonomics of the AK rifle while maintaining its main advantages; high reliability and ease of maintenance.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
  	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A custom model developed on the basis of AKM by the American company Rifle Dynamics. Chambered in 7.62x39mm. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_am17_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]AM-17 is an assault rifle that uses standard intermediate cartridge 5.45?39mm 7N10 cartridge. It was developed and manufactured by in the late 2010s by Kalashnikov Concern based on the Yevgeny Dragunov MA Compact Rifle. The weapon is intended for use as a close quarters weapon.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_amb17_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The AMB-17 is an integrally suppressed assault rifle that uses a heavy subsonic 9?39mm SP5 cartridge and armor-piercing SP6 cartridge. It was developed and manufactured in the late 2010s by Kalashnikov Concern, based on the Yevgeny Dragunov MA Compact Rifle.The weapon is intended for use as a close quarters weapon.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Integrated suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ash12_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The ASh-12.7 (ÀØ-12.7, which stands for "Àâòîìàò øòóðìîâîé 12.7ìì" or "Automatic assault rifle, 12.7mm") battle rifle is a dedicated CQB/Urban Operations weapon, developed by TsKIB SOO ("Central Design and Research Bureau of Sporting and Hunting Arms"), a subsidiary of the KBP Instrument Design Bureau of Tula, Russia, by request from the Russian FSB (Federal Security Service). The weapon was designed with extreme short-range stopping power in mind because it is intended for special units of the FSB which operate in urban environments against heavily armed and organized gangsters and terrorists who need to be killed in one shot. According to the Russian press, the first batch of ASh-12.7 assault rifles was delivered to the FSB.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium Sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] CKIB ASH-12 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The DVL-10 is a lightweight and compact sniper rifle in proprietary and current military subsonic calibers has been developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional accuracy and range are needed.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62, CQBSS, MARCH-F, PN-23, SpecterDR, ACOG x4, SUSAT.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The DVL-10 is a lightweight, compact, and silenced rifle in proprietary and current military subsonic calibers and has been developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional accuracy and range are needed.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62, CQBSS, MARCH-F, PN-23, SpecterDR, ACOG x4, SUSAT.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DLV-Type compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_grach_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP-443 is a short recoil operated, locked breech pistol that was developed for the Russian Army trials, codenamed "Grach" (rook). These trials were started by issuing initial requirements for a new military pistol in 1993. Several designs were submitted to the trials and the winner was the pistol designed at the state Izhevsk Mechanical Plant by Vladimir Yarygin. This pistol, initially known as the 6P35 military index during trials or the MP-443 "Grach" manufacturer's designation, is adopted by the Russian Government for military and law enforcement use under the PYa designation, and already issued to some Russian Army units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Modified automatic grenade launcher complex OC-14 by local artisans from the "Duty" for one of their former fighters named Danya-Master. The machine is assembled for all cases of the zone, the caliber has been changed to a more common one - 5.45x39, there is also an enlarged magazine for 60 rounds and laser. This machine gun is a long-standing dream of every veteran of the "DUTY" group, but the former owner of the machine gun said that only the most worthy member of the group would have it in the end, and instructed Petrenko to find a new owner for the machine gun.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Modified automatic grenade launcher complex OC-14 by local artisans from the "Duty" for one of their former fighters named Danya-Master. The machine is assembled for all cases of the zone, the caliber has been changed to a more common one - 5.45x39, there is also an enlarged magazine for 60 rounds and laser. This machine gun is a long-standing dream of every veteran of the "DUTY" group, but the former owner of the machine gun said that only the most worthy member of the group would have it in the end, and instructed Petrenko to find a new owner for the machine gun.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 compatible grenade launcher (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp412_descr">	<!-- details shows 2 avalaible sights but there are none -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The MP412 REX is a Russian double-action .357 magnum revolver with a break-action chamber and an automatic ejector. It was designed for export (REX, Revolver for EXport), but never put into full production due to lack of a market. The weapon was designed by IZHMECH, the state-owned Russian Izhevsk Mechanical Plant, which also designed and produced the Makarov PM semi-automatic pistol.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered for 9x19 mm Parabellum.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PL-15 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_tan_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered for 9x19 mm Parabellum.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PL-15 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_pl15_scolaz_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered ib 9x19mm Parabellum.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low) (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PL-15 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_tan_pl15_scolaz_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered ib 9x19mm Parabellum.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint T1 (Low) (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PL-15 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm">
		<text>PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_short">
		<text>PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_siber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zenit_siber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces. This model has been manually altered to include an enlarged ammo box. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-V compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zulus_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This weapon was previously owned by Zulu. Its special features include an enlarged ammo box and a particularly reliable retracting mechanism design. The modifications meant an increase in the weapon's weight, but that wasn't a problem for the last owner.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-1S-03 Kobra sight (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The PKP "Pecheneg" is a Russian light machine gun chambered for the 7.62x54mmR round. It is a modernised PKM machine gun. The Pecheneg is said to be more accurate than all its predecessors due to a heavier, non-removable, forced air cooling barrel with radial cooling ribs and a handle which eliminates the haze effect from hot gases and keeps the barrel cooler, making the weapon more reliable.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_siber_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A modernized PKM machine gun chambered for the 7.62x54mm round, said to be more accurate than all its predecessors due to a heavier, non-removable forced air cooling barrel with radial cooling ribs and a unique handle which eliminates the haze effect from hot gases. Currently in use by Russian Army Spetsnaz and, though it was developed mainly for infantry use, is often fitted to light vehicles.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for dovetail mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-V compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rp_descr">	<!-- wpn_pkm in debug mode -->
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Fitted with a skeleton buttstock made from wood as well as a hinged buttplate and a wooden pistol grip. The rear part of the buttstock houses a cleaning kit, and a disassembled cleaning rod is stored in the right leg of the bipod. A very reliable machine gun.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The RPG-7 is a further development of the previous RPG-2 anti-tank grenade launcher. The RPG-7, in its first version, known as RPG-7V, has been adopted by the Soviet army in 1961, and is still fielded in Russia and at least 50 more countries. By far, RPG-7 can be considered as one of the most successful anti-tank grenade launchers ever made. Initially thought of as an anti-armour weapon, it was later adopted for other fire support missions with the introduction of other types of grenades, such as anti-infantry HE-FRAG and multi-purpose Thermobaric/FAE. The RPG-7 is a shoulder fired, single shot, smoothbore recoilless launcher, grenades are loaded from the front, and the rear of the barrel is fitted with venturi nozzle. Due to the recoilless design, the backblast is dangerous. The RPG-7 is usually issued with 2.7X fixed magnification optical sight, designated PGO-7. It is a simple and inexpensive, but possess a high threat to modern tanks and can also serve in a number of other roles, making it a flexible weapon.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PGO-7V.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 5.45x39mm. Key features of this kind of weapon are - quick detachable barrels, enhanced ergonomics, weaver rails on the handguard and dust cover.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A model developed from the Komrad 12 gauge semi-automatic rifle for hunting and protecting members of ISG research teams from mutants. The weapon has both a dovetail mount and a picatinny bar for use with various types of sights. This model has a new type of trigger mechanism , which allows firing in two rounds burst.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Salvo 12 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Saiga modified by Mercenary request. Chambered in 12 gauge. Additional Picatinny rail mount for various optics and a massive muzzle brake compensator installed which significantly reduces recoil.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Salvo 12 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The Serdyukov semi-automatic pistol chambered in 9x21 mm.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_gurza_up_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]chambered in 9x21 mm. The Serdyukov semi-automatic pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Trijicon RMR (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR1MP 9x21 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_sr1upgr1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]chambered in 9x21 mm. The Serdyukov semi-automatic pistol.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SR1MP 9x21 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x21mm. The SR-2M submachine gun is designed to engage enemy personnel using body armor at ranges up to 200m. Its main advantage is high firepower, high accuracy, and high stopping power at close range.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny/Weaver rail (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GVZ-SR2 compatible suppressor.</text>
  	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x21mm. The SR-2M submachine gun is designed to engage enemy personnel using body armor at ranges up to 200m. Its main advantage is high firepower, high accuracy, and high stopping power at close range.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon can be upgraded with a tactical kit (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KP SR-2 reflex sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GVZ-SR2 compatible suppressor.</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_sr2_upkit_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 9x21mm. The SR-2M submachine gun is designed to engage enemy personnel using body armor at ranges up to 200m. Its main advantage is high firepower, high accuracy, and high stopping power at close range.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n		
        %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] This weapon was upgraded with a tactical upgrade kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KP SR-2 reflex sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GVZ-SR2 compatible suppressor.</text>
  	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sv98_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SV-98 (Snaiperskaya Vintovka Model 1998) is a Russian bolt action sniper rifle designed by Vladimir Stronskiy. In 2003 special operations troops were armed with the 7.62 mm 6S11 sniper system comprising the SV-98 sniper rifle (index 6V10) and 7N14 sniper enhanced penetration round. The rifle has been used in combat during operations in Chechnya.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PKS-07 scope (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]A hand-assembled version of the SVDm-2 sniper rifle with improved mechanisms for increased flatness. Little difference in appearance, but provides an ideal combination of accuracy and stopping power.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1P59 "Hyperon" scope (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tritium front sight.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_pmc_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Dragunov sniper rifle with folding stock. Was specially designed for Russian paratroopers and special forces units. In the Zone similar models are usually used by mercenaries, Ukrainian special forces, various PMCs and other power structures for conducting special operations.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTS-62, CQBSS, MARCH-F, PN-23, SpecterDR, ACOG x4, SUSAT.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Rotor 43 7.62x54 compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_nimble_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The SVU-A is a variant of the SVU rifle capable of automatic fire, designed on a request from the Russian Interior Ministry. Although the weapon is generally not suited for close-combat situations, the automatic fire has proven itself to be a reliable emergency solution for exposed marksmen. This particular model of SVU-A used to belong to Max, the legendary guardian of Freedom.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1M, 1P29 "Tulip",  EKP 1S-03 Kobra.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SVU-Type compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Chambered in 7.62x54mmR. Dragunov sniper rifle with folding stock - the SVDS variant. Was specially designed for Russian paratroopers and special forces units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various scopes for Warsaw pact mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-V compatible suppressor.</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_isg_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This rifle was devloped off the VSS Vintorez. Chambered in 9x39mm. One of the main differences from the original is the presence of a special mechanism that allows you to fire with a misfire of two bullets. It has an picatinny rail installed along the entire length of the weapon. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Canted Trijicon RMR red dot sight (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS/VAL compatible suppressor (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP30 "Guard" compatible grenade launcher.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m1_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]This is early prototype of VSS Savant. Chambered in 9x39mm. This build is more popular with pro-stalkers because of the lower price than the final version.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Integrated VSS suppressor.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m2_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]Developed at the request of Mercenaries, a team of scientists led by Professor Sakhorov brought this gun to bear. Chambered in 9x39mm. Twenty gravitational artifacts were used in this rifle's development and as a result, various qualities of the gun were improved to a greater degree.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Various sights and scopes for Picatinny & Warsaw mount (check details).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tactical laser aiming module.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VSS/VAL compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vssk_descr">
		<text>%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2]BlackMarket: %c[d_red]Warsaw •••\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]The VSSK is a Russian bullpup, straight-pull bolt-action sniper rifle chambered for the 12.7x55mm subsonic round. The weapon is also known by its other name, Vykhlop. It was developed in 2002 for special forces units of FSB.\n \n
		%c[d_green]  • %c[ui_gray_2] ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Cortex 1-8x, Barska ES AC10632, ACOG x4, EOTech 553.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] VKS/VSSK-Type compatible suppressor (integrated).</text>
	</string>
</string_table>